I'm going to blink it.
There we go.
I got it.
It's just me.
It's like, hey, you coming up here?
Hi, hi.
Hi, look.
Lola, you want to say hi?
I'm back here. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm
I'll you to send a few bucks. I'll show you what I'm just kidding. I'll show her free. I'll show
Okay, okay, so I'm not gonna do anymore beers. I had too many beers
And thank you smelly
What's wrong babe, and one more cigar
Are you showed it you saw it? Oh my god. You're good. She's really the same. Are you sorry enough smelly?
That's for you smell smelly. That was just for you. It was just for you
If this for you you like that you like that I know you like that
Melly's smelly's fine. Okay guys smelly's good
Can't show any more without a donation
Yeah, I'm very vulnerable here. I'm in a speedo
You guys coming down to the last bastion of underwear the speedo you're there hey Lola you're there
You're there Lola Lola who are you looking over this you're looking over the your rail
You're saying you're looking at Lola. I see you. You're looking over the rail here. She's coming. Yeah, that's just Lola.
Oh my god.
Look.
What are you looking at?
Tricks! Tricks! Tricks! I see you. Tricks!
Tricks!
Tricks, I see you. Oh, that's Lola. That's Lola. Lola!
Well, are you marking it tricks?
Tricks you over there on the table. There's a trick over there
Tricks you over there on the table
ignore the guys
This is so much cat drama. It's so much it's so much drama with the cats. I can't take it anymore
Yeah, I just want to say goodbye to you guys. I just want to say good night
I'm in my speedo. Hey challenge and I'm just in a speedo. I'm not going to show any more
So embarrassed
How did my butt look good my butt looked pretty good
Betas, thank you for stopping by. I love you. Love you too, beta
You like really keep my speedos. Thank you. Thank you
Easy got me the speedos easy got me the speedos
I'm going to dance for you dance for you. Oh my god. Oh my god. That's too much. That's just too much
It's your choice. Oh, hey beat uh
Guys there they cover everything they cover everything everything is I see my legs
Every woman that joins podcast is slurped ten weeners. What what are you talking? I
Dirty more than you think here
This is a guy in the speedos. I'm a guy in America. I'm just a missus Schumer and speedos
Embarrassing this is like look look look my leg
Cover barely
Cover I'm barely covered
Yeah
Did you go over here? I'll shoot you one more one more. I don't know everyone's saying would you one more?
There's my last beer. I have one more. Oh, I do I do. I've actually three more home three
I'll just take a regular half and half or each. I'll take a peach
I mean he's mild good
I should ride my e-bike wearing the speedo. I will oh
It's so good in it. Oh, it's so good. Stay clothes. I'm in clothes. It's they cover everything
Nothing was shown
What's wrong tricks tricks what's wrong tricks you're upset tricks
Mirror mirror, what's wrong? I'm wearing a speedo
Yeah, what's going on face come over here face over here once face over here once hi
What's wrong speedo?
No, oh
You're near Lola that Lola up there home. There's Lola. I see Lola
What you're the catnip catnip. Oh, she's been the catnip
No, you like that. Oh, Lola
This is watching. Okay. Well, are you high?
Guys, let's look what's to watch
Yeah, you're really high
Okay, pet you and pet oh pet
When Quinn go go go for it go for it. He's a catnip Lola. We're watching
Yeah, oh here she goes. Oh
Lola, no, I hear you outside. I hear the door outside. Yeah, there's there's Lola
Lola
No, I see you're eating catnip
You're there you can't
Guys if I didn't don't know I will I will dance my under out. I'm wearing speedos
I'm a recovery up covering up for the rest of the night. I
Show everything
I'm bearish things
Hey, you come in the covers. Hey
There she is look
Guys join the panel
Send a don't know if you want I'll dance, but I'm not gonna dance for three
What's wrong fix?
You're good. You're gonna be that. I know you're good
You're you're the north you're the north yeah, I hear the North you
What good night covers good night covers tricks
tricks
covers
one
No, that was there. What was there? Okay, because I'm
Low is there
Lola you're fine
Okay
You just there guys
Good guys
Guys I look so good. Oh my god. You're good. Okay. There's so good. Oh, yeah, like guys is perfect
Okay, I'm gonna covers. I know I'm sorry. I'm sorry
I'm sorry guys
You're hanging out with me. Come on. Make a motor
You guys
Oh, baby. Hey, babe.
I'm showing it to Lola and the covers. Lola, you're on the covers. Hey, Lola.
See you there.
It is there. I say be that you be that black RG. You saw man. I'm a speedo. I'm so sorry
AT
I'm sorry. God guys. I'm sorry
They donate I got donated for this be that I'm gonna wear them. I
Look, I look good in them though. I look good. I like better than I thought
Hey easy cameras on you saw it you saw
Easy, I mean I'm even the mileage out of these
Hello
Well, come on come on Lola you come out
Look what she thinks come here. You won't come out. She won't she won't there you
Come here. Oh, there she goes. There she goes. Oh
You know
Lola
There oh, she was friends. You ran. That's how the cat loves me. Oh, she loves me
Lola, you're getting me out of the blanket. Oh.
Well, who's this? Blumers? Hold on a second.
Hi. Good morning.
Hi, how are you?
I'm doing good.
Oops. Good.
Here I am right here. I turn the I turn the echo off
I'm gonna come up here and
Nice to meet you. I don't think I've been on your panel before you haven't
No, my name is Rusty
Rusty, okay. My channel is called platform boots
Platform boots. Yeah, you know even those platform boots. Let me know guys
I think this person is a good person.
I sense a good person right here.
But from you, you are.
I am a good person.
I think you're a good person.
Thank you.
I'm coming up because I have a lot of people blocked
in the side chat,
because I just have a lot of people blocked.
So I'm gonna ask you if I can address the side chat
and what's going on there.
What's going on? Tell me
I just see a lot of people talking about
Different things that have been happening with my friends
But I'd noticed that they've been on your panel quite a bit. That's Goddy and JT and rain
Yeah, your friends or your enemies. No, they're my friends. Okay. Yeah
So
Anyway
I just have a song for you.
OK.
I hear them talking, talking about people.
They're saying something.
Let's give them something to talk about.
How about love?
Does that make sense?
That's a good one.
Let's do it, let's do it.
That's bunny rate.
You sing now, now you sing a song.
OK.
Have to think
These girls are passing by
They tell the tale of men
I'm not waiting on a lady
I'm just waiting on a friend
I just waitin' on a fan.
Yeah, yeah, hi. Yeah, cuz I've been going on these panels and people are like well, we don't know you we don't know you so
But whenever I go on panels, it's usually when people are screaming at each other. So I don't get a chance to talk really, you know
But I've been I've been in the drama before
Not
So have you seen me on my speedo?
No, you haven't and you want you?
Yeah, I was going to ask you if you had bottoms on when you said you were going to
There's all I have is bottoms. I just have
Short hair bottoms. You want to see?
No, everybody else will see too. Oh every every us was fine
Wait god bless America
I'm going to bed. I'm going to bed. Oh, booty. Okay. That's enough. Stay away from me. Oh my God. Oh, he cut me off.
There you go. You have full reign of the show. Okay. So, who's going to come up here and confront me about anything? Come up here, Hannah. You're going to come up here and confront me?
Play for boot. Hey guys, I'm still here to let people on. I'll be backstage, but
You know, I want to yell platform booth platform boosts are ready. Yeah
Come up and confront me. Hey tombstone gamer. You want to confront me?
Who wants to confront me because I know you guys are dying to confront me come on now
They won't confront me on my own they won't confront me on my own stream either
They won't I mean guys come on
For your opportunity just scribbles
Scribbles, are you on scribbles? No, they don't
Okay, he's here's his arm with his wife tonight. He's a really cute guy. We were arguing his
Wife is yelling at me
Today we're yelling each other. Yeah, she went she fell asleep. He fell asleep next to her. They're they're on live right now
Livestream hunter versus rusty rusty
Boila she she said I didn't pose anything that breaches you. I know you do the better not you better not
I miss Liz hi, lady, baby
He what no, no, let's not talk with you. Why are she?
Miss Liz
You're gonna come up RG RG you discuss it miss Liz is my bestie
This is Liz come on up guy guys. It's less heraw. It's 4 30. It's all I'm not to get a
Meta watch this job with my speedos. It's gonna be very embarrassing
No paneling it's gonna be very embarrassing. It's gonna be very
They look at me weird in any way. They're like, why are you coming up here? I'll drunk on your e-bike
Falling outside being a coffee every morning every morning
Now I'm gonna go my speedo there and you're like, they're all the police to be shibby you're there
You need a bathory or lay back baby
Yeah, we need it. We need people in the link. Oh here. We have Jeff here. How almost I get Jeff wants to talk to you
Do this guy?
Yeah, I do
Okay. Yeah
Hi Jeff
Simpy pet. Hi. Hi
Spend a long time as I say hi to you
Yeah, yeah. Oh, this is what you look like Jeff. Oh, that's what you look like. This way look like yes
That's Jeff's real picture. It was really cute
Actually, Jeff is is a attractive guy. He is he's straight. Are you straight Jeff or no?
Yeah, I'm sure he's straight. I straight
Damn it gosh darn it gosh darn it
I love the hat. JT, do you want me to say by saying was Rusty who supplied you the
Everyone's laughing. Yeah rain. I'll ask them a bit of respect from JT. Is the rain here rain here?
You do it every once
We're on the channel asking like many times to verify
Propose anything. I agree rain rain. No, just your boyfriend rain wild with his panels rain rain
I know I know
That's you know
You too. Yes. Oh, and you guys talk for a minute. I'll be right back. Yeah. Okay, I
Don't know why you're picking a bone with me. I've been exercising. I've been doing live streams on an exercise
and oh
I just said come up here if you want to confront me, but we don't have to confront each other
I'm not gonna confront you
No, I mean I know you
Yeah, I don't are you gonna if you want to talk to me about Hannah, then we might have a confrontation, but
And see you I don't have anything against you. I will always want the best for you Jeff. Yeah
That's true. That's true. Yeah
You don't get to talk to me because we never because you are if you go on a panel
It's usually JC's and I don't go there. So we just don't I mean, I know you got thousand channels. So it's hard to keep up with
Everybody's complaining about all of these channels. I have
Listen, let me explain something. The channels are not
The channels are only for one person and that's what made the channel for so I don't expect anybody to follow them or
Or but everybody complains about them because I think that they think
that I'm
wanting them to follow them and
I don't care only only person I care about is following the channel is the person that I made it for
Yeah, and everybody should be
Following what I'm doing because the reason why these people all have their individual channels is because they try to take my channel down
If you try to copyright strike me or do any of that bullshit, I'm gonna make you your own channel
So you can't fuck with me. Oh, and that made people really mad
Made them really mad, but don't fuck with me. Don't try to take my channel down
Well, I'm the only channel I only knew of you made that one channel pay girl. That's it
Because a girl brought it up
Yeah, Hannah, I've known Jeff for a long time like longer than you like way longer than you I
Don't pick it Jeff
He's a troll
He could be irritating, but he's been pretty good lately. He doesn't do anything, you know
Too raspy
Jeff I think you're a good guy. I mean you rode your bike yesterday. I think that was
Yeah, everybody didn't think I had the balls to do it. So I did I did for three hours
Yeah, that's cool. Yeah
And I'm doing it again today around like 10 10 30 or 11 ish
Oh neat. Yeah, I'm gonna show downtown because they're expecting some sort of bullshit political riot down there
Yeah, so let me address the side chat
For some reason, there's some controversy about this video of somebody's kid.
Yeah, that's my business and I provided that to anyone else that wanted it because of the
of the kid's father. So if you want to get in the business of that because somebody posted
that video, you need to come after me. I'm the one that got the video.
I'm the one that was involved with the dude for four years. So
All your bullshit we you think JT's new at this or whatever. No, he's not
He's not new. You can't fucking drag him into your fuck shit. Okay, cuz I'm gonna start getting involved now
Yeah, and you're not gonna like it
So you want to talk about posting videos of Jarl's daughter or whatever you come after me
Yeah, I bana
Live stream advertisement ready come on up here come up here and confront me about it
Okay, whatever. You know what? Yeah, you're right. This is getting too deep for me
I did hear that he was posting the video on people's channels
But the thing in the comments or whatever
But the thing is don't fuck with him and then you won't then that won't happen. That's beyond me
That stuff's beyond me
but
You know, I mean, I don't understand how you people think that you can just talk shit and fuck shit and talk shit
And go on panels and talk your shit and accuse and get your nose up in everybody else's business
And then when you get retaliated against it's fucking pearl clutching victim time fuck that
I'm not gonna allow you to do that
You ain't gonna do that to me you think you're gonna do it to me, but you're not gonna do it to me
Easy welcome to my world
Don't start none won't be none is I think the motto, right?
You guys decided I watched you do it you guys decided that you were gonna focus on JT for posting a video for of a kid
That's your fucking bugaboo. That's your fuck shit. You want to start with him? I
See ya I see you
None of us are new to your stupid fucking drama
We all know what the score at least I do I've been doing this for seven years
Celtic I
Cut my chops on the boy none of you people can even measure up to the boy whatsoever
You think you're so tough with all your IPT bullshit all that
The boy is your papa. The boy is the grandfather's the elders the grandma's
We set the bar on all this fuck shit drama that you guys think that your kings and queens have now
Midnight you cracked me up man
Don't start none won't be none
Hi avocados avocado avocados I don't know who that is
It seems to know everybody so I don't know they
That's avocado man from Jayce's
No, it's a different person. Oh, I thought that was avocado man
See as I want that's a Goddy
Turn on your camera, turn on your camera, turn on your camera.
No, I've never turned on my camera, ever.
I've made two videos of myself.
I've had because.
I put them up for people to copy and nobody ever copied it
It was obviously me in my car flipping everybody off right in the face. Nobody ever fucking clipped it
You're so desperate to see me, but then when I fucking post a video of myself, you don't even clip it
I just made another one the other day
But I caught myself because I don't want,
because when I was filming myself,
I immediately flipped my finger up to the camera.
And then when I was watching it back,
I was like, you know, I don't want to be this person.
Somebody's actually...
So I didn't put the video up.
I didn't say you did.
No, no, no, I'm talking about a video I made of myself.
But you just literally said that if anybody has a problem
with posting the video, they should address you, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I would be okay.
What, what, what, what else?
Okay.
Hi, Chris.
You guys are totally echoing.
I'm gonna address you.
When I mod somebody and I ask them,
you can only like post like, whether it's like, you know,
What does that mean I
Don't know
So what no no, but you said if anybody has a problem with that being posted to address you, right?
Yeah, I don't have a problem with like whatever you guys do whatever you're doing and like fighting for justice
But when I say to somebody I don't want to post it on my fucking channel and I've given them a wrench
I already took it from them and then I give it back to them on the promise of do not fucking do that kind of
Shit and they say I can do what are that the fuck I want is then your responsibility mine or theirs
Uh, I don't, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I
I don't know. I don't know.
I mean, in your side or whatever.
Before you don't know what happened, I'm going to tell you what happened.
The whole issue is that link was posted on my fucking channel
when I want nothing to do with that fucking crap.
And I'm over and over.
I don't want to deal with that kind of bullshit.
If I trust them, I don't want it.
No excuses.
That's not enough.
You know, I know I'm going to talk down to you.
You are a person that wants to fucking do all this moderate drama with all this drenched bullshit.
So you must be new.
Because if you're going to sit around and everybody's fine,
I can do whatever I want.
I
Want you understand, but you're not gonna post a link in my fucking channel without my permission period
That shit's echoing, right?
Hey Arthur, what's up?
You got the echo miss. It's me
Yes. Yes. Okay. I'll go back and come back. Okay
It's okay. You can just stay back there now. Yeah, this is a boot over the boots. Oh my god. Oh my god fucking echoes killing me, bro
Thank you, I thought I was tripping out you but boots to the other dude that was here Jeff
yesterday, I was listening, there's like a shitload of new people around this sector
over here.
I'm going to ask you guys all kindly to like, please don't ever fucking join again.
You guys are all fucking boring.
Go back to the JC, WC channel, go back to the Space Odyssey channel, go back to wherever
bull shit, okay
we're not here to talk about
I want to talk about the baking
I want to talk about the cookie
no
we're not here for that gay bull shit
I don't know the drama
but he's not down with that gay bull shit
I don't know the drama or whatever but like she instantly came on here
and she's like promoting her channel
like fucking quick style like fuck it
here's my channel like right she came on dude
like fuck get her out
who did that
It does not mean that you have to hit the link and join
Was it platform
Who came on like rise like I got on here. She's like, oh my channel's platform like uh like fuck like nobody gives a fuck to you
God enough of the fucking random
What are you talking about surrounding Arthur? Who came up here to platform or like advertiser channel?
I want the same end of the world. I want the elbows of the world
Wait, I'm talking to you. Who came out from one of the elders
We want those of the world enough of the bullshit
Yes, I
People here on panel and none of them provided a single
Joke nobody made me laugh
thank you, thank you
you are all fucked and sucked
just because the link is out there
it doesn't mean you have to join
you don't, please don't
Arthur, can I keep laughing?
you can make you laugh Arthur
dude, what the fuck bro
you're letting some random
what the fuck
so you missed all the content earlier
what were you saying
who was up here to promote your channel
yo, what the fuck
I mean you smile. I mean you smile at least you smile
That's the that's the underwear that he sleeps in bro. What's a big deal bro? Yes? Are you deaf?
Are you blind or you stupid? I'm asking you a question. Who is up here promoting what channel?
platform boots for a rise that came in she came on and she's like
I've never been on here
what's going on
she's right there and excuse me the guy
am I supposed to stay off a link
that's a dude that's Arthur
song what are we doing here
am I supposed to stay off a link
nobody cares about this elder shit bro you just show this song
oh you know okay I thought we were looking at Arthur
I don't know if Arthur is wearing like boots like cowboy boots or like
Barefoot I can't tell. Oh my god. We need the elbows. It's a goddamn icon. It's not cammed up. You get it?
You know, but what is it? Is he wearing shoes or is he not? Is he barefoot or?
No, bro, he probably just treat the random icon on his phone dude. Like, you know what I mean? Oh my gosh. Here's what I mean, bro
I'm just confused. You were talking about booze
Jesus Christ
like
He did like the best fucking
Fucking spread eagle. Are you dumb? Everybody saw it already. I don't I don't see your channel 24
He did the best like praying mantas like spread eagle that you ever seen on your life
the
that's where you are sorry
what the fuck
no no do that spread eagle doesn't pray in my test
get that butt
this is Arthur
you need to get that shit embroidered with
your channel name bro and sell those
sell those
where does your back end psyche
that shit flat as hell bro
he's skinny motherfucker
I think you should get some tattoos on like your body where there's your back and psyche good
I mean look I'd rather be skinning the fat, you know, so fuck Barry, you know, I'd rather be skinning in fact
Well, Peter
so what I wanted to say about me and you is
I've been like defending you about Shannon because Shannon
Did the same thing to me. So basically you're the new Rusty to Shannon
Because I know I get it. I understand like I appreciate that but again what comes down to when I tell like JG
don't post shit in my fucking like a
Chat and I've always told them like I told them like several times if you're gonna post something
Tell me what it's gonna be. He said it's gonna be a cat video. Don't post
Video is going to be controversial. That's it. Oh, it's nothing against you and they're talking about it again. What's the point?
Because you know you're talking about it again
Well, what I really meant by the video is not who's posting it in your chat
I just meant I thought he has possession of the video
And I have position on my channel and I have position of who I give lunch to or not Jesus Christ
Okay, well, you know who like what what happened like that the nursing home opened the doors like what is going on?
If you saw me if you actually saw what I looked like
Dude, you wouldn't be saying I was in a nursing home
Sleep good
Well, oh my boy, you're part of the problem like just because the link
And then if I come on the panel, I'm promoting my channel
Shit about your channel
Everything you people bitch about everything
You guys listen you guys hear about the fucking shooting in Vegas the Vegas shooting right in front of blasio hear about that
Yeah, are you okay? Are you okay Chris? I'm good bro, but I knew I know both those fools
I like I didn't like never meet them, but I knew they're I knew that I love them
You know on YouTube and shit because of a you knew of them
Yeah, I never fucking met him, but I met one of the dudes that's friends with the other guy like in person
But anyways like that shit's crazy like people like you know this internet shit fucking that was his job
Dude the guy took it serious and this other motherfucker was spent years
Just like you guys talk shit on the internet like motherfuckers. He he he didn't he didn't play dude like and that's what happened
He's like fucking that shit's real dude like some people take it serious like internet fucking shit, dude
Yeah, and that's what happened
You have to be careful
Yeah, when you're in a foreign country and you talk a bunch of shit to people all the time like Hannah
You know Hannah says she lives in Australia or whatever. So nobody can touch it
If you go to with the dude's channel the guy that got shot like you go to channel like a half of it's like making fun of the other guy
Yeah, I mean like yeah, it's like all bad like fucking
And he like, you know, that was his job. He was trying to get YouTube money being a streamer in Vegas, you know
Whatever blah blah blah and fucking uh, you know, that's what happened
You know, I mean and he's like trying to claim self-defense now, I guess or whatever, but I mean, that's all that Chris
It gets pretty it gets pretty it gets pretty dicey when you when you actually get yourself
uh getting shown shooting somebody walking up to them and shooting them and their wife
yeah real great yeah okay why were you freaking but it's pretty interesting
it's a pretty interesting story behind that why were you doing that i read i read on the uh
you know i listened to you a couple times on panel the guy that got shot like have like the
randomness got hit okay nevermind somebody's talking about let's say cars cheese meats and then you'll
like I was probably like super drunk I it's not sure I was super drunk you've done it so many
times why did you fake having Tourette's I don't I mean if I do it's just the way that I was drunk
at the time and said something I don't have seen you way too many times and you'll be like word
and word and then you'll be like grandma's pussy fucking the pussy like I don't know man cute by the way
Okay, granny anything else you've been a great oh, I'm not a granny. I'm not a granny
Okay, thank you for calling
Okay, you run this shit. Do you have any last words here? Do you run shit here?
Have any last words?
Do you run shit here? Yeah, those are my last words. You have a good day here. Have a good day. Thank you. Thank you. You don't run shit. You don't run shit. I can tell. I can tell you don't run shit. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank
Well, all I gotta say is that fool that fucking did that shooting, bro
Like I look I look at the dude like the dude that did the shooting
I'm look I'd like see I look watch his vods right now, right and he's probably been to prison
He's probably fucking good like felonies on his record. He doesn't know about
I'm talking about the Las Vegas fucking shooting where two people died
I missed the days where this shit just just was like, you know, you know, you know
You haven't heard about it in random joining the fucking panel bro. You haven't heard about it
Listen real quick
The elder verse Jesus Christ real quick here on top of the fucking space Odyssey over there make me
You know 24 seven on the music go go back over there, please
Listen, if you haven't heard about it,
you know, Las Vegas, the Bellagio,
this full fucking murdered two people in front of it
that were live streaming, there was a YouTube beef.
Okay, I get it, I get it, okay.
Thank you.
Well, that's what I'm talking about,
if you don't know.
All right, Chris Kay, any last words, you too, bro.
You asked, you asked what we want to talk about.
Once you shut up.
The most of you are just a snoozefest,
I gotta be honest.
Shut up, motormouth.
The most of you.
Shut up, fuck up, motormouth.
I mean, I would just, no.
I'll stop talking about it. You know, it's all good. I'm just like
Period because this guy's got a fucking motor mouth and he he thinks he runs shit. So
Fucked up granny
So I'll be changing diaper, is that what you want?
What's the apartment number you're looking for? Let me know
I can always call 411 for you. Let me know
Man, I almost want to throw some cards out flat for me flat boots. I almost like got a vibe for me
What?
Like that retail card
Throwing cards. Hey, what are you fucking David Blaine? Yes. Yep. All right, psyche. Finally psyche
What why have these random people just joined fucking
Everyone I know Chris K. I know beta. I know
I have platypus and I know, I know, I know Arthur, I know every year.
Like all these people from the elderverse man, they know how to fucking ruin a panel real quick.
I normally, I normally cam up dude, but I have issues right now with my computer, my hard drive, like I pretty much failed, I'm on my phone.
So that's why.
Find out what that X button works, let me know, find out what that X button works.
I mean, I'll leave dawg, it's all good dawg.
No, no, no, Chris K, Chris K, do you want to see my speedos or no?
Oh my god, no.
There we go.
No?
See what?
of the
If somebody were to eat your ass right now, how would you pose?
Arthur stop!
I know my Facebook!
Are there other stuff stop getting gay other stuff
Only thing of GT nothing gets you like you've always been killed when I
Just shut up for a minute while I talk so I apologize, but you did like actually
Do me like dirty and that's it. I'll end it at that. It's like no big deal
I'm not gonna be like scorn forever. I'll just get over it. Just like we gotta learn
You put on the speedo it was like an olive branch. Yeah, it was all it's all over it should have all breads
Yeah, you sound like you're
And then I was like he just like he like he's doing it for you
Yes, are you drunk
John
It's American flag
How many screenshots did you just take
This is a drinking stream, bro, we all fucking drink here, dude. Yeah
Except the other one up there boots she says she's a little too old for it shut up
Yeah, everything is fine. Everything is fine. Everything is fine. Everything is fine. Yeah, yeah, I'm old. Yeah, I said shut up
Yeah, I'm for calling anybody old and I'm sorry if you got mad at me
I know that you're you know, I just wanted just like
Time to be apologized in a week. I'm sorry. This is all I ever hear from you. I'm sorry
I love you. I love you. I love you. I apologize. I love you. I hate you. Well, it's like I came
a platform you know you know somebody named like Catherine I'm a
Catherine you're Tracy. I'm used to it. I don't know anybody named castron. No you came on me you're like oh
Beata and you have double a standard. I said look
The reason why all these people are around here now
Shut up. We're talking about Catherine. Who's Catherine?
I don't know, there's some where the K, like Katie, Katie, Catherine, or like Karen, maybe?
Is that platform?
What is the shit about this fucking topic, bro?
Those are very, like, typical names.
Thank you.
Now I'm on the platform.
Oh, my God.
Oh, she didn't say anything.
I'm on this whole thing.
I'm getting nice. She didn't say anything. I might have hit the nail on the head, bro
Like I get by I get hella vibes, bro. I'm not gonna follow. I'll tell you
What are you talking about? You just said three names. You said Kathy Catherine Katie and Karen
Platform you know those people
People here fucking what about them
I want them back on panel like I miss those days where we used to like fuck around with all these people now like all you older people are around fucking 40 50 year olds like this is
so what what does age have to do with intelligence because if you are young I'm not talking about intelligence he likes older women he likes older women
it's a reason to older women don't worry about it you guys talk about fucking tubaware he's into cougars
All right, so yesterday salmon was live. Oh
That's what he wants to talk about nigga nigga nigga nigga nigga
That's what he says all the time psyche. Well, get her out of here psyche. That's what that's what Sam and that's how they talk
It's okay just saying
Stopped it because everyone can say the soft day every every race can say the soft day. It's okay. That's what's in the heart
You are okay
Black actually the soft is soft. It's okay. Well, that's I know that she got clipped. I'm gonna start sending that everywhere
Oh, no, yeah
That's how he talks
wait, I can see the picture better now, okay, so he's no
He's walking with no
You have no shoes on. Well, hey finish your story. What about what about Sandman bro, right? Thank you very fresh
So say man, you know, he had a key and all these people yesterday
He was going to Kate as per usual and I'm starting to get this feeling that
All he ever does is stir the bullshit just to go live,
just to have those people join,
and just to have those people kicked by the $25,000 donations.
Okay. And I'm here to call you out, Sam.
That's what y'all do.
Let's watch it. We're younger. OK. OK. What do you deal with?
What do you deal with?
Fucking diamonds, pearls, jewelry.
I don't I don't get out of here.
No, no, no, I don't do that stuff anymore.
You are right. I am retired from drama.
We say you said you see a bulge.
What do you mean by like yourself? How about that?
Like what do you mean you see a bulge?
Hey, you know
Picture
He saw a bulge on Arthur's
Right there. I see you right there. Oh, I thought you mean with your speed. Oh, I thought you meant your speed
Oh, we're I mean, we don't see nothing. What are I have one of my mind's you I'll show you
Yeah, that is a horrible tattoo you have in your chest like a bow tie in the front I mean like
Can you not tie it?
No, don't be sorry. That's how you make me laugh. That's how I miss you. Anyway, I miss it. I miss you. I love you. I hate you.
You love that. I'm sorry. I love you.
Arthur, you miss this boat.
I listened to your panel.
Arthur, you love this boat, too.
And you talk a lot of shit about Psyche behind his back.
I talk to you. How is it behind his back when it's on a panel?
Because you go on your stream and you talk to him in the bottom.
It's public, bitch.
And then it's not behind it's in public when he's live
you go live and then you're like shut up with your stupid ass like
their foot is only cares about this about the money
if it wasn't for me psyche wouldn't be stripping for you right now
only cares about the money he's just changing the money
Yeah, I'm gonna leave if you don't strip for us. No, no, no, wait, you're coming in. Oh
Arthur Arthur he loves don't spread eagle spread eagle
Don't do that. Please don't do the praying mantis again
Arthur this is for you. Arthur. Don't do the praying mantis. Oh, what the fuck?
Whoa
That's for you, that's for you.
Oh no, I'm out of here, dude, I'm out of here.
Bye, have a good day.
Thanks for calling in.
Oh good, now we can talk.
I know, thank you for calling in, Arthur.
I love the praying mantis with the American flag.
But Arthur Arthur made Arthur made me do it crazy. That's okay. Arthur made me do it easy
Bob me the speedos guys look easy Bob me these
Yeah, it's your fucking it's your own fucking house or whatever bro if you want to like sit around and speedos all day or whatever
It's your idea. I do I want to
So yeah, I got by give you props on that shit do what you want
Yeah, I feel like I got therapy actually actually I got therapy. Okay. Okay. I'm sorry. Sorry
No, I like it because it was so much. It just made me laugh. Yeah, Chris was right. Just relax. I'm fine
Okay, dude, you know I mean it's like fucking some I sit around my house all day naked sometimes you like what gives a fuck
It's my shit. It's my choice. You know me
Thank you look like
Was she like backwards with the roly-poly
the
I'm sorry, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have to hold my mic, I have
It's just under we got
Guys, it's under where it's under where it's underwear. Okay guys. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. What's going on?
Yeah, you're probably sitting on the beach dude. I would fall I'll wear that show. I'll show it show everything off
Memphis are you everyone's mad?
I just a lot like that like dying over the flirty diamond in person
Guys remember for a diamond for a diamond one like this today. I'm gonna snub her salt
That's what happened. I said, we all saw it. We all saw it. We all saw it. Yeah, I see
Fucking I live in Vegas dog. I see people like walking down the street like that
We're saddles on and that's it be like fucking you know, I mean
You know, I don't give a fuck
You know, you're left 20 minutes ago if you're about you psych psych school
and he's not been on the cool like fucking respect for me like I don't care
if I would show I would show them it you know
I'm sorry everybody I'm sorry I'm going to be a speed up and a hashtag I'm sorry I'm sorry
guys guys I love these pills easy guys easy guys these for me guys you want to see what you got me for
easy you missed it
oh easy guys go through you
Yeah, he bought that for me. Are you fucking serious? Yes, he did easy on camsid dog
Yeah, he sent them and he doesn't want to take the link
Easy get up here get up here easy easy you bought them for me
Come on take the credit for making me laugh
He didn't he didn't do the Amazon, but he like sent me the cash out for them
So he's in he said over the over the price there. So
Pull the back part up to my crack one
Yeah, he did no Celtic has a request okay Celtic
Oh, man. Hey, man. You gotta wipe. Hey, you gotta wipe your ass better. Oh, no. Oh my god. What's the bad? What's the bad? Oh my god. I've been really
If you have a problem, take it with easy.
Sikey, didn't I say everybody would love him though?
Didn't I was telling you?
Yeah.
He wants no, he really wants no body boy for them.
I'm going to buy him a tarot deck too, don't worry about it.
Do you want him to do all that though, easy?
Yes.
You want him to do that?
You want him to go like what he did?
Easy, go ahead.
Back together, everybody's having a laugh,
it's funny, bringing the numbers, that was the goal.
Easy he's he brought me a job step. I was like, no make it a speedo. I'll just pull it up
I'll pull my crack as like I can't
Yeah, he did what are you gonna put the bra in like another night? We had that was good tonight
I mean today was good the bra for them another day. I have a nice buck guys a scum a scum is shot
Oh my god, I'm sorry Brian King. I'm sorry. I seem a lot of we blame you easy
It's going to put on his glasses and he's like zoomed down.
He's like, oh, it's like, you got to give him the 360.
You know how to do it with that pole.
Yeah, I like it.
I don't know.
It's a good pole.
He's from New York?
Yeah, from New York.
I don't know.
There's a hole.
Easy.
You bought this one easy.
It has a full front.
It's pretty easy.
That's where you easy
Don't be embarrassed like every time every time he stands up, bro
That's you got a tight nice. That's why the string there. Do you got tight?
It would be cuter if you tied it to the side and not to the front like that
It just looks like drawers like like do it to the side like bikini or something
So you're saying like it should be string like snow string at all
No, I think the string should be like not on the front tight like you know a dork like a fucking like you you know
Just pull it to the side like make it like bikini like sexier, you know make it like an accent. Well, those are thick though
That's thick. That's not like fuck
Yeah
I know the tie
No, wait the time oh come on thank you. I just
Oh my god
It was barely
You need a you need a full wax now
Easy can you play can you pray for the brisly come dead you guys
the
Oh great
Holds no, no, no, no, not yet. No, just keep it like the way it was and then just take the tie
Just tuck the fucking just tuck the strings in that way you can't even see them right
Yeah, like something like that or like we're getting to a little
Yeah, I can't stop laughing I snored it
Everyone everyone like everyone's but everyone's having fun
Everyone everyone
Everybody in the fucking building your eyes is out of cry with tears or in pain from seeing it either or you cry from laughing or cry from seeing it.
But God bless, oh shit.
I can't, I can't, guys, I gotta cry. I think I gotta cry.
Alright, I think I got it out. I think I got it all out.
I think so
Nice, I hope he doesn't do it again cuz I'll just play
If you buy if you buy me a speedo, I'm gonna
Easy, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I was for you, I
that's like that uh jackass bro uh the dude that wears the speedo and he starts dancing to people
i got clawson you love it like it and you might get more of it you heard
i don't want him anymore and i'm gonna i can't anymore i forget who it is but he has a speedo
on he puts a radio down and starts dancing with people with the speedo on jackass
of the
Know you're talking about did it crash?
No, I mean stevo's probably warren speedo, but it wasn't him either
It was other guy wearing the speedo. He got the ball head with the speedo. That's why it's not this content, baby
It's all those
Wearing a speedo looking jackass back in the days my man. Yeah
Yeah
There's their ball sack their asshole. I mean I'm in a speedo
They were showing everything
And then our chair and and uh, what's the name? I saw I thought what's the name?
I saw all the other but I saw the other butthole. I said everybody's butthole everybody's
Nobody's had my butthole yet. I've seen all of theirs and their dicks
is that the guy's party his name's party boy on jackass and he like he goes to Japan he like puts it like a wireless like
a radio down good quality speedos
they are like grip apart
well no there's a bad idea
go take a screenshot go take a screenshot
go put you at the picture latino god
screenshot
American spirit
tuck in the uh tuck in the strings
whoa whoa he got a little bit of cheeks
I do I have a little bit. It's a little bit. Oh my god. I'm really embarrassed. I'm just up there
Chris K. What's the tie at home?
Hi, and fucking tuck it in bro that the people are tripping they don't want to see the strings hanging around right you think I've had if you like maybe not
I'm good
For you I was for you Chris
that's all Chris baby
I'm good but you know I mean I think that in a chat the viewers like it right
they love it they want more of the gift that keeps on giving it's great thank you so much easy
really really welcome you're welcome to everybody who's having a great laugh right now you're welcome
You know, I would say this I didn't talk to a psyche for a week
But that's Peter got us like to renew you died again
The tie we bonded and yeah, it worked. Thank you so much
easy and psyche I
Hope like he never does it again though
I've been on a New York vibe lately man. Yeah, you know Wu Tang
the more you tell him not to do it
I know it but I don't listen to it
I watch the show, that's what it's about
fucking method man, red man, old school
wu-tang bro where he's like fucky
I saw him on the street, he's a fucky
and he's like fuck me
just sit there with your shirt
I'm not gonna show it anymore
it is patted though
it is patted
easy got me the extra padding
Take take the strings and
Give me a second give me a second first for panelists and chat. What's the percentage?
I think he's gonna come home with somebody a picture of it. It's very patriotic guys
He go out to the beach right now on summertime
It's bigger at late easy
Did you really fucking shop for that? No, he did
He said that's the one he wanted. I cashed out to him right there. I said if you buy it on the spot
I'll pay for it on the spot, you know, that's it
But he bought it himself. He picked what he wanted. He knew what he wanted
What's going on here? Hold on. Who's has that pictures you know psyche? Who's that?
That looks like a fucking female. That's pretty sexy actually.
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I
You're like what are you doing like that?
No, like wait. No. Oh my god. Oh my god. What are you doing? Oh my god. I'm so sorry. That was so embarrassing
Oh, but I didn't do anything. I didn't do it. Nobody go back and flip that nobody please nobody because we're not weird
Guys, I'm wearing a speedo
You can make any pose you want and look like I could put it man my head. They can't
see
You guys, there's a pod that's covering the genitalia area.
I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you
I mean, like I'm like I got chest hair. I'm a little hairier than you. That's why I'm just what I'm saying
No, I'm very here. See
I got I got are you telling me if you wore those same as bikini there'd be butt hair sticking out of all the sides
I mean, no, no, just I'm talking about like it's chest and like
My chest yeah, that's my this my hair is just
very hairy
My guy hella hair, but uh
the
no but I would I would do it I would get it
you do it so you have to put your legs in your head
and let a Mexican woman
put wax in your butthole
and then you have to sit back in this
no it's not it's usually Asian
no I'm saying Asian
do you trim your section
do you trim that up or no
no no no
I go to
Korean women
I have Korean women do everything
real women do everything
Okay, so you do like that's why your shit's like fucking like a hairless
Hairless, I'm a hairless. How hairless is that the hairless?
You're fucking you're fucking, you know, I mean you're setting your section
Money for 20. Uh, this is like morning time. This is how you started your day
Okay, you started your day enjoy it, you know, you got some buns get some coffee. Yeah, everything's covered. Everything's
Guy is called it's called a garment. It covers everything
Guys, you can wear that in public bro. I see people all day walk around Vegas like that. I can't I can't yeah
Yeah, you can definitely on Fremont Street. Yeah. Yeah
No worries. I need to lift weights. My muscles are big enough, look at my muscles.
They're like populous. They're like gantic.
How much are gantic muscles are?
I don't know where these fools are from in chat, dude. They must like live in their house or whatever, like go outside.
People walk around like, like psych all day, like on the beach, you know, right near the beach.
Not a big deal, yeah. And Cali, not a big deal.
Nothing.
The funny thing is like how said he did the poses. That's why I was laughing. It's not a big deal
You guys and remember it is pride month. He's representing
United States with pride month. It's cool
Everybody enjoy
So or the TOS the TOS and don't show your
Issue with this you got to take it with easy on count. He's the one that paid for it
Yeah, yeah easy mommy the speedo
Don't show your butthole your public hair or your wiener and then you can show everything you want
I can do I can put my head I can put my head on my head like that. It's fine
They said it's fine
is that a spine?
Can you stop doing demonstrations?
No, I'm not sure.
I'm going to do demonstrations.
I'm doing...
What's been going on?
Nothing much.
What about you, Chris?
I was sick like the last four days.
Dude, three, four days.
Boy you had the flu or something? Yeah, I had the flu or like I
Did not eat anything
But I swear to God like I had the flu and a couple of miles or homies out here in Vegas had it too
Which I did not even make contact with them, but like I got it around the same time
It's like going it's going around out here and I haven't been that sick dudes
Since I had COVID like fucking four or five years ago, whatever it was
Yeah, it sucked dude. I was like fighting for my life. I was like man, I can't believe it like fuck
I had to take a couple days off of work
And uh, but I'm good now. I thought you were trolling the chat. I'm sorry. Um, I
Thought it was not I thought it was a fake one because I went on your channel is like said sit like six subscribers
I was like, that's not press K
That is my that's all that that's my youtube
But I don't stream on youtube like I've been banned multiple times on youtube and this is only this is my you the youtube
Did I use just a type type and chat?
Yeah, yeah, like YouTube. Yeah, so I think I mean I stream on rumble and
This yeah, that's my the YouTube the one that wasn't talking to chat. Yeah, just to type in chat, you know, yeah
I'm not trying to stream
I don't know what's going on in Vegas, but
Yeah, dude, it was YouTube streamers that had beef over the years and this fucking guy like fucking doesn't play around and
I guarantee you like I just by looking at the dude. I've probably been in prison like he probably his
Fuck the fuck to like be you know, he's he's he doesn't fuck
He doesn't like a people think it's funny to talk shit on the internet
But you got to watch who you talk to like that's why I really if you look at me like when I talk to people like I
I don't say anything or make any threats anybody unless I kind of back it up type shit
So fucking he's like probably the same way and like fucking this guy like he fucked around and found out because like even though
It's like oh, you know, I'm not gonna go like, you know pop anybody off like that, but you know, I mean it's like
He fucking took it serious like his you he was trying to like he was getting money
Like on streaming in Vegas like on YouTube and like this other guy was like fucking with them and like he lost subscribers
like he started getting hate because his other guy was hating on him and
You know
Literally that like, you know streaming was his life
Yeah, the whole shooting was about like, you know, we're we're fucking we're on YouTube right now
You know, I mean we're a fucking I'm a youtuber. We're like streamers
these guys were like fucking out here they were fucking they had beef dude and he like he just like I eventually snapped I guess dude and you know it took both like the guy and his wife out he like I can't it blows my mind on stream it's like dude you know I mean it's like fucking it was it's like there's a video of it and it's like it's all it's all bad it's all fucking bad the guys literally probably gonna go to prison for like life like without the rules upstairs
yeah well they need to yeah he does that's crazy
You probably go to a mental institution too and present well, no
I think the way because I watched before they deleted his channel. I watched a few of his videos his
VODs or whatever and like he
Like he doesn't fuck around dude. He's like Mexican. He's like, uh, you know, cholo like a fucking, you know
What's up homes? Like, you know, he doesn't play dude, and I know I know that's I'm from San Bernardino dog and like fucking
Some people will fucking shoot you in the goddamn parking lot of a gas station if you look at them wrong type shit
You know what I mean? Yeah, like fuck it. You know, I mean, it's like you mad dog at me homie
Well, you don't know where I'm from dog like that guy is like fucking he doesn't play type shit
And he was a youtuber and like fucking he that's what happens type shit, you know
That that's all I got to say about it. Do the full side thought it was funny to make fun of them or whatever and like
You know and then he found out dude. It's all bad. It's all back
Like in reality just not even on the internet. We all could have been like probably
Fucking killed by having conflict or like fights with people like several times
whether it's like road rage or like
Just like being like drunk and you're like you want to fuck like you want to fucking like let's go
You know, you never know how crazy people can get but yeah, you know, you know about it
Like there's just beef you have beef with people like I've had a little beef with people and shit like that
This guy had beef over like over years. I guess he got pepper spray his wife got pepper sprayed
By this guy earlier and like he's just been fucking like it's an itchy trigger finger, dude
Because that's how he plays I I suck some of his thoughts. He has a
SF
Giants San Francisco Giants like tatted on his fucking farm. So he's probably from Northern, California
Like Cali fools like you know if he is then fucking you know, he's probably been to prison
Like he's just maybe he his channel fucking he's not getting money to pay his rent his girl left him
He's his life. It's fucking his life got fucked up and he's like fuck it. He's like he's one of those homies that will fucking
Fuck I'll just go back to prison type shit. He's like fuck it. Dude. I'm done type shit pop pop pop
Fuck it lock me up. Like you know what I mean? He literally turned himself in after this shit
He turned himself in well
What you said like I don't know the story, but he said fuck around and find out if you're gonna engage like oh
Pull up with me. Let's meet up. Let's like fight. Oh, they might you know, just fucking
Like I you know people out here that I know with like some streamers out here have talked shit to me and like fucking
I I don't forget. You know what I mean? So it's like I don't I don't I don't I don't
If you hear me talk shit about somebody like I'm gonna back it up type shit these fools
What's up
You're saying that you would to you would do the same thing. No, no not saying I would do the same thing
I've never like, you know, I'm just saying like if people have said that to me
Out here some of the streamers out here have said that to me, and I'm just like
Really like fucking, but you know, I mean, I'm not gonna like yeah
I'm just saying some fools don't play dude regardless if it's the internet like fucking the dude has like you know
When he streams he had like fucking I don't know
Do you I was raised to defend myself like if somebody attacks me?
Yeah, I will fuck you up, but I will not like just hit anybody
And in the same like thing where if there's like somebody crazy
That's I was raised the same way if somebody's crazy and they're gonna come up to me and they're like I'm gonna fucking kick your ass
I'm gonna fucking do this. I want to do that. I'm gonna be like just like oh god
the
Dedicated to making fun of this guy and all this shit and they used to strike each other's videos and like get them fucking strikes on their channel
Blah blah blah, etc. Dude like these fools like had a beef for a long time like fucking over streaming, you know
And like I said, the guy's got multiple videos over here just like saying like, uh, oh, uh, because I strike this video like he's over here crying and like he like puts like, you know, images of like this guy like some guy crying like this is this is the guy Fanny or what's his name, whatever Manny cried.
This is what he's doing right now because I strike this video. Ha ha ha. It's so funny. Like he's, you know, yeah.
You know this is like a wake-up call for like internet live-streaming
About this like the other night Chris it was right before it happened. I think it was a I think it was yesterday
Right before it happened
Or I'm eating something Carl was on the panel Carl full and we were talking about the John Smith shit
And people were like Vita why are you mentioning?
I was like well because this shit can get really fucking scary and serious then as soon as I said that like three hours later
This whole like episode happened in Las Vegas
yet people this is like a this is like a wake-up call for people on the internet in general like
Watch what you say to people on the internet because they'll they take it serious and they you know
This could happen to anybody bro people get swatted
Or whatever else dude, you know, I mean this is
the dude the dude was he was like a hardcore he like he was trying to like
Which is what everybody every streamer wants to do right make it they want to fucking be a streamer
They want to get money. They want to have that further full-time job
This guy was that's what he was going for dude and this other guy was like fucking this shit up
You know, I mean multiple like multiple videos vods of him just like fucking fucking him up and like he's like
You know, he just fucking it's he snapped you might have just had some issues in his life
And he snapped and he's like fucking you know, I look at the guy and I could guarantee you that he's fucking
He's been the prison dude like that's the type of guy you see in prison like that guy right there
I would fucking I would see him in prison like fucking
Doing burpees with the fucking South Siders and shit, you know, I mean like I would you know, he doesn't care
He's probably like fucking he probably has it arranged
Also, I heard he has like donators like some fucking donators that fucking like
Don't mark don't quote me here
But like gifted him like a core like a corvette or something like he had a car that he got money
From a donator that fucking hated this other guy
So there's like shit like that too. You know what I mean? Like he had a you know, so he like
It's like you know what I mean? It's like a streamer fucking
were these like big or these like big fucking streamers like do they have like a lot of subs I think they had around like
20,000 or something like that maybe a little bit less 16
The one dude's channel is gone, but the other guy's channel is still there. I think I haven't I've even checked dude
You know that's fucking pathetic and sad. Yeah, have you seen the video of the clip?
I know I saw like a shit in the news, but I don't like to like go into detail with stuff like that like watching
You know, I mean don't watch it. It's just like it's like blatant like seven shots dude five in the guy
Yeah, it's that for me. I'm just like I'm very visual
So and the girl the girl sat there and watched her husband like you know get popped five times
And then she got popped twice and the camera falls. It's all bad. It's all bad. It's like damn that's fucking
You guys hear the cat purring or it's like you hear it. I
Mean that shit was like three miles away from my house, you know, I mean and it's like I knew I know
But I knew both of a new of these streamers
But like I've watched their streams and all they do is like walk around and like just walk around and like not even
Make any of them. I
Didn't know him personally, but I know of their streams on YouTube and I've watched their streams
I was like, what's this guy about I watch him and all he does is walk around for like hours and like
Not talk to anybody like I used when I stream IRL in Vegas and shit. I'm like in Iraq with people
I ain't a fucking bringing people back to my house type shit. You know, I mean like a I
Talked to everybody, you know, I mean these guys just like walk around and like stream like the buildings and like Fremont Street
And everybody else but them, you know, they put I'm sure they put they put the camera on themselves
But it was it wasn't the content that I'm that I do, you know, that's why I don't I do I'm not even doing IRL anymore, dude
Like I don't know
Kind of
I heard that a couple times like after this they're like fuck that. I don't want to meet up with people
I'm not doing anything like yeah. I heard that like yeah
I mean, it's like I feel like they especially in Vegas. They might
ban selfie sticks or ban like it's like fucking like streaming because of this dude. It's it's not a
It's it's making it putting a bad name
On streamers out here, you know in Vegas. Yeah, it's crazy duck. It's fucking
You guys hear the cat purring I don't want like I can like you hear a cat purring
But see like another scary thing that can happen was if you meet up with like
You know like that happens all the time, too
If you watch like any of the you know like this crime things
people meet all the time on YouTube like couples, you know and
That shit happens. This is like over the internet over the internet in general they meet up and then fucking
The lady the girl that met up with the guy the ladies like missing
You know or or like maybe she's crazy, and then she's like
Is obsessed and she'll get her ex to do something to that other guy. It's like yeah all this fucking should happen
It's real shit, dude, you know it's real shit. That's why I don't like that's just the way I am bro like I'm not gonna like
don't say shit unless I'm fucking gonna like do it or mean it like you know I
mean I don't I don't like to joke around on internet I look at the I look at like
I don't I look at it different than other people like you know if LD if LD ever
fucking joins I always will leave I don't want to be on the same fucking what
happened what you don't like LD I don't I saw clips of him like doing shit that
I've seen him also, you know, like trying to fight for whatever that's like different things with whatever, but no, I really don't I don't like
Hey, that's my Ellie's my homie, bro. So I mean, he's you know, he really provides nothing to the table
Like he just will sit here and just like you
He doesn't even fucking stream dude, he doesn't like like me in a way like me
He doesn't give a fuck. I cuz I really don't
I don't I just I can think LD is like a male whore and has like no self-awareness and
in like he works, dude, he works like fucking a job.
And he doesn't focus on when you drink.
I don't focus on this shit.
I don't focus on streaming or whatever he does now.
But when he used to drink, he wasn't thinking about his actions.
And like, I drink, but I'm always like, OK, I got to, you know, this is
he didn't give a fuck.
He I don't know.
I don't like L.D.
I gave him a chance like months ago, but you know what I don't like is like I told him many times like
I don't want you on the panel
It like causes a lot of issues for me and you like when he joined and he just like wants to put me in the middle
of that shit as usual like people
Yeah, he doesn't care dude. He doesn't like
Stream, you know, he's not trying to get money like I know like a psych's trying to like
make it this YouTube bigger and like maybe get you know money from the which I respect
but uh
Yeah, he's like it's just like me dude. He works. He just gets on here like like I'm right now. I'm bored
I'm not Albert doing
He's the where's he at? I think he's in the
Lake Lake where yours tickles Albert like you know like
Being extra love
Oh my god, I thought I was gonna see Albert and I saw Psyche's crotch
I was hanging out. I was hanging out. I was so sorry. You're so funny, Psyche. I'm dead.
I might, I might come up, but uh, my fucking hard time. Come back, Psyche. Come back, Psyche.
No, for a second when he was like, hold on. I was like, I was looking for a, like, where'd you go?
I'm here. I'm here. I'm here. Oh my god, it's like 6 a.m. where we're at, Psyche.
I know. It's time for a coffee. It's time for coffee.
I would normally like camera, but I'm like on my morning America. Yeah
Yeah, it's good morning America. There's nothing showing
My hard drive my hard drive on my desktop is like basically dead and I need to get another one
And like literally reinstall windows and I just haven't done it. I've been busy
So yeah, so I'm like literally on my phone using my phone data
and that's why I mean I'll come up, you know, maybe, but
I just don't normally don't get I don't normally like this kids Albert from you just give
BKG says we love you Albert
You love the other kids
Anyways, Chris, it was really good talking to you.
I hope that you feel better.
I know you already do, but take care of yourself, Psyche.
I never laughed and had so much fun in my life,
even though everybody hates me and they're like,
you think-
Nobody hates me.
Everyone loves me.
Everybody's gonna judge me on you tomorrow.
I mean, whatever, today.
Who gives a fuck?
Let's just enjoy it.
Chris, you're gonna do that?
You're not gonna do that, Chris, are you?
no, not Chris Chris doesn't judge like yeah, no, I'm what is I don't even know what she's a you know
She's saying she did something wrong. I didn't think she did it. Yeah, what who cares?
Why are you sitting like sophisticated with a fucking pipe like Sherlock Holmes?
What are you doing psyche? Hey, so you know a put listen put the camera further away. You get full body shot. You know me
it that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that
like from from a for the
the window can walk
Chris, this is for you. Oh, you got a couch couch in the way
No around you got a dance around don't just sit sit there do like a dance bro like dance around
Like turn on some fucking uh
You know why I am CA and then dance around bro
Similarly what Chris I got you just what do you want?
Well, you have to like you have coffee. I mean, all he's doing is just putting a like full like crotch shot
I mean, it's like what do you want? You're with the back. He's with the back
He really likes the patting on the bulge. Wow
Never mind never mind. I'm sorry
I'm trying to make you happy. You can't please you. You should like dance like dance. Do you want me to dance? I'll dance for you.
I'll please that. I'm happy. Sing a song. You want me to dance? You have to rap a song, Chris.
I'll just play a YMCA, dude. YMCA is not a good song. It's not a rap song.
Chris, this is for you. Chris.
I mean, I'm just saying what I would do if I was like if I was him
I wouldn't just be standing there with it would it focus on my fucking
Copyright music
Chris you like that you like that Chris
He
Yeah, he's in the workshop. He couldn't handle it anymore
He could I know it's it's too sexy. I know I'm too sexy. I'm too sexy for my show
That's a good
Thank you, you made me lost so much
With that tricks all trees wants to make you smile, too. Hey tricks
Did you see many mansons many mansons in a card with the Lenore and tricks and
Lola on it. You see that?
No
Chicks is back
Traces back. Yeah. Oh, so I'll find the hole. Oh my god. It's so cute
It's not it's not
So it's right here. So this is for me. Oh, I can't show it. Chris came back to many mansons. I'm a sticker
This psyche of the many Manson
Wait, that's like a CD
It's a little sticker and then this one sticker
Psycho sticker. I like it here. This one is the Lenore
Tricks and Lola. Oh
My god, it's so cute
Oh my god, is that laminate it? Yeah, it's been a full full
Full limited thing. It's a car. I want one. I want one. We can mama Lee
There's one Lenore. There's Lola and there's tricks. Oh, it's so cute
Yeah, my shit actually hit the fucking wrong button dude, sorry
the
I like the American I like America dude, so I like that. Yeah, and um, I would do I would wear I would wear one too
Maybe I'll get one and stream I'll stream myself where one
This you would you know
Hold on
the
I'll get you the same American flag. We're both for American flag. It was this is flag
You got to like help me you got to help me like it maybe we could try to try to pick up chicks
Yeah, no, no, I will help you fit into them. I'll talk to people on the beach for you. Whatever you want
Whatever you want. Yeah, I mean that would be content that would be content. Okay. Yes
Guys, it's a deal Chris is gonna get a speedo guys. You just heard it for here first Chris is gonna get a speedo
We're gonna go speedos down the beach
We're gonna hold hands eat fish tacos very
Comfortable with his sexuality
Yeah, I'm one of the times I've streamed out here in Vegas. I went to like a gay bar
I went inside and sat down and talked to gay guys and they gave me their number
They bought me drinks. They fucking the bartender like they all let me stream like
I'm you know, I was like, oh, it's cool. Do you like I'm not I
Like I like pussy type shit. Does I mean?
But I have nothing
You always be responsible for what you did to psyche with the speedo
So you there's no way out of this like don't say you did for the content people. No easy
You did this for whatever
Is it easy easy easy said how much of the speedos?
I'll give you this more. He sent me three cents more than I paid for them on the cash. So there you go
You got me the speedos. You did easy. It's okay
In a way in a way you're a man of your word, dude
You could have took the money he sent you and just said you fuck you to him, right?
I'm in the speed again. I'm still wearing that like I'm like
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
he's he can't even be on the panel anymore
You know that's another reason why I respect
That's another reason why I respect site cuz like fucking just because of that like somebody sent him cash out money
He actually did what he's the what the person wanted him to spend the money
You know I mean a lot of some people would be like fuck you and just like take the money and like I ain't getting shit
You know look at the easy goods. I don't care beat up. I don't care what people say. It's okay
I don't care. I did it for the content. We know easy. It's okay relax
We're just teasing you at the same time. It was fun
God calm down. I mean we know just calm down
We're happy
Easy just take it easy. He's married. He's married. He's married. Yeah
Is this one? Oh, here he is. He's going to say hi. He wants to say hi.
Say again, go put that picture. Don't kick me out again. I think he's got me or I lost service.
Easy, easy, easy. Stop.
Psyche loves us so much. He's going to do one last pose for you.
You forgot you forgot to lift the right leg lift your right leg
That's for you
I'm comfortable I got family and friends is like that don't bother me people in my neighborhood grew up like that
Like I don't care. I don't I don't want to wait now. I don't want to wear the speeders for us the this is the only outfit for us
the year
I'm gonna start by I'm gonna start by wearing this
The easy easy. I'm the same way, bro. Like fucking anybody that's tripping out or whatever is like a homophobe or a fucking
Or some shit who gives a fuck dude. That's
Homophobe, why are you here if you're not ready to see psyching do this?
Yeah, I mean fucking
Bitch
No, nobody was I'm just saying bro. This is what this is what spike does like he likes to sit around and
Yeah, no, no, I will
Stream bikini
Well, are you happy?
I'm happy
I care about you're happy. I don't care about nobody else if they mad
Jealous, whatever the fuck whatever the fuck it is. I don't I'm jealous cuz I didn't get bikini like that, but I'm happy
I'm happy
You should a beta beta beta you should get one
With a padded
You got to show me and then I send the money on cash out. That's how I do it
You gotta buy it on the spot
How did you find a bikini that's got padded clutching?
Well, it's not
Listen, I don't want I don't want you to get it confused. Listen. He found it. He showed it
Yeah, he's staring at it
you're welcome psyche
Yeah, be that you should get like a bikini like I'm married like American flag like that and wear that shoe
I mean it's a summer honestly, I wouldn't be caught dead worrying and I'm
I mean, no, no, personally, I don't
be happy who you are.
No, no, I like bikinis, but I wouldn't even wear a Persian
flag because I just I just wore a lot of black.
Think you should stop
Attention like wearing an American flag bikini walking around
You live in America, bro. You should wear one
Everything is covered everything is covered everything. It's all you see in the legs
That's where you be that that's where you be
I like that. Thank you so much. I'm proud.
Ain't this your month? You got to do your time.
You have a good budget. You have a little baby bond.
You know, you made me giggle and easy. Great choice. Yeah.
Yeah, I agree with easy. Great choice.
I tried all week, but I lost it off tonight.
What's wrong with supporting what somebody wants?
Yeah, exactly.
That's not exactly what nobody says.
Yeah, throw me baby.
I don't care.
Don't.
If I would have known he wanted that, I would have bought it for him too.
You were saying for like two weeks, but I think yeah,
I was going through back and forth a lot, so you probably didn't catch it.
I just want to know when like he's gonna wear the top. I know it's not going to be tonight
It came with a top piece. Yeah, it came with a top. Yeah, it's padded
I
Don't
Why would he wear why would he try to wear like a fucking top like he's got to I thought it came with like a top piece too
It's a two-piece. Oh, it's just be those beaters. I thought you bug it
Well, I thought that had a thing was like for the move. Wait, it's just
Did you see his wish list?
Doesn't have a top
Wishlist in the back chat for me. No, dude, like there's guys, you know that wear fucking thongs, dude
Like why does it have to have like a top for like, you know, no because originally when you
yeah it's a guy it's a guy it's a male song dude there's isn't there's basically what it is
it's a male it's let's be precise it's a male swimming trunks there you go there you go
i got confused because there was pad there and i thought it was like a padded bra top and then
you know how bras got the pad to block your nipples from popping out yeah and then you put it
they don't they just wanting to see like a lot of sense now I was like what kind of bikini comes with like padding in the front
Oh my god
You know you want to have a speedo on it stops for the boats for the kids
Okay, I still don't know I know what she's I know she's talking about she's talking about because there's Speedos that are like
Super thin where you could actually see
Now they have to improve now
You're a little patting, but I have no idea what I'm talking about.
So I'm sure you can still get those ones without the pen and then
he did the opening of your unboxing easy or whatever on my panel.
When he pulled it out, it was like a patting and then he put it on his head
and I was like, is that like for the top and then
He I thought it was like a top part and he trusted to the side. Well, I could say this I could say this
It's kind of weird. Why would there be a bikini with like padding in the front?
You know, I don't know screen and a string to tighten it. I could I kind of it's kind of weird, right?
Yeah, it was it's all confusing, but it all made sense. I'm dumb. I've never seen one like Mikey. Where are you?
Remember I keep saying is that like a top? Oh my god, you're muted
You're muted Chris K will tie this dream with his mouth. I'm a wrongo, right?
What now I mean, no, I
Okay, you'll tie this room with your mouth, right?
What?
No, okay, okay. We're gonna tie it. You're gonna tie it, right?
Okay, hold on
all I mean here's the thing bro if I would say like if I'm hanging out with you bro you're streaming or something and somebody like donates
I'll do it for content type shit, but that's I mean that's about it. That's about it
There we go
Just get run the run the rabbit hole. Listen. Listen. That's my listen. That's my problem, bro
I can't do IRL because I fucking get in trouble dude. I fucking I uh, I know there's an audience watching and I provide
I provide content like that. You know, I get it. I get arrested. I get fucking all this shit
Who cares?
Who cares if you think you're gay, you're the straightest guy in the world who cares
Yeah, I you know, I like I like pussy. I don't care if you know, we know, we know, you know
You know, so I'm not you know, I would do it for the content, but yeah, I'm not trying to get all
you know are you are you just like you did you see this and you thought that you would want to
Not because you're gay because it looks comfortable like in me. It's like he happy. It looks like he's just like born again
Yeah
Now you go back three panels and you'll see how drain and tidy was yeah, it energized them all
I mean, uh, I'm trying, you know, I'm trying. I'm getting burnt on Vega. I said this before to you guys. I think he said, he said, it's okay. Okay. Okay. Oh, look, look, look, look, look, I think it's okay. I said I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay. I think it's okay.
Couple a couple of last parts like a chair. Just chill. You don't say never know I'll go never don't push games
Maybe other way, but just no no no, I know I know I know he is but I say one day one day easy one day
Have one day with easy
I'll go party with you I'll take you guys I told you early
I'll take you out you said can I go to Puerto Rico just I'll take you my family in Puerto Rico
We have a blast. They be like by Lamarico
You know
That's what I'm saying
Can he wear the bikinis when you take him to the beach?
All I want is what I want the chicken feet
I want you to cook the voodoo chicken feet and then fool me as a white person and say oh the white person
No easy easy. You're funny. You're good people. I like I like your style
I had to come to conclusion too, you know when they was like you could get soup from being
Easy easy easy I went to your house and thanks. Give me dinner. You sure we chicken feet
No
He was doing voodoo shit on me. He was doing voodoo on me. Why is your family?
Why would you think you would have chicken feet?
Why did you why did you make chicken feet? Why did you make chicken legs on your on your big TV dinner?
Why are you talking about thank you? Yeah, I want the easiest family in Dominican Republic
They used to make chicken feet
I didn't get Puerto Rico
Grandma's laughing at me say oh look at this gringo. He's eating it
Have you ever had chicken feet?
I have in there. They're like very oh my god. They're very they're very not a lot of meat around the bones
But then all the grandmothers and mothers are left. They're like, oh look at the gringos eating chicken feet
But why do you think like what why do you think like easy would have chicken feet?
I would never have chicken feet. I don't deal with that
No, his grandmother is in the movie. I'm trying to curse me
the
Get easy said. Oh, this is the appetizer. Wait, how wait, I just have a question you try chicken feet ever in your life
Easy have you ever eat chicken feet ever?
Yeah, yeah, when I told you to eat chicken feet did you eat it?
He said it was the main course
It was a delicacy
I'm just trying to figure out how you eat chicken foot, but you don't eat pussy
I'm going to try anything at least once
That's all I was asking, you had chicken feet in your life before?
I don't know. You was gonna have a Lola Lola. Do you change the subject? He's had chicken food before. Hi, Lola
Wait, she can't be beautiful. No, she doesn't want chicken food. Oh, okay. She doesn't like chicken food either
What's wrong
Okay, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I'm sorry. I just saw chicken feet. I'm just laughing. No, no, thank you
We need one for one special person
Are you maybe you're
We need a pose for Alex you got to do a different pose
Listen listen just for Alex different pose just for Alex different
Alex's favorite pose. Oh my god. No, no, no
Welcome Alex. I was just a Alex. Special. Special delivery, Alex.
See you guys, I gotta go to sleep. Easy. I can't. I can't.
I don't know. I'm gonna fucking off. I don't know what to do with deal.
After what you just did tonight.
Beat it. Beat it. Stop playing. Stop playing. Stop playing.
What you want, Beat up? What you want?
I don't know. I just, you're the instigator.
No
Guys, this is just my it's a rare show guys rare show. This is just normal. It's normal
Okay
Nothing weird about this. Oh my gosh
There's their recordings it's packed right now. They got a delete old recording
Yeah
The shooting in Vegas
To be told I want to talk about that I got a resemblance of similar issue
You that's what I'm saying, bro. Like they had YouTube beef and their live streamers
Yeah, I mean there's a whole situation, bro. Like I got you know, I lived it. So I know
Yeah, I mean, that shit was three miles away from me
I knew who these guys like I didn't meet them in person, but I knew I knew about their streams and
It's like fucking some people like, you know, you'll listen recipes to the family
Yeah, it's all bad. It was told whether it was trolling or not and
Rest in and rest in peace to home because he going to be in life. He body somebody. I you know, I ain't I never body nobody, but
Yeah, I feel like he's been to prison and he'd like he maybe like I said
I've been a prison bro. I've been through that. I know everything you described about him. I live that life, bro
I live you. That's why I don't want to talk about I live that life everything you describe
Yeah, it's all bad, bro. Like that's why yeah
People again, this is like a wake-up call for fucking internet culture in general do some people don't play
Yeah, yeah, they have kids didn't they have a good kids and shit
It's all it's all bad, you know, I mean, it's like fuck dude like that's you know, I that's why I don't I
You heard me earlier what I said earlier
My thing is stop trolling because we should get real
Shit get real shit. Yeah, some people will fucking yeah
That shit that shit is wrong is wrong in a whole lot of ways and
You know say what about me and I can't even break it down like this it could be
Mad possibilities. I'm not gonna break away. Yeah, I mean it wouldn't doubt said like this has happened before
This is just blown up because it's like literally like you could there's a video like live
You know
Yeah, that's it was this life dude and when you have like an audience
viewers that fucking you know you getting hate from one side of the fucking casino I know all about it, bro
I know about this shit. That's why it's like
Hey, this is gonna take the help took out what but at least I own up to mods so it is
Yeah, I was young dumb and I'm full of cum. Hey, man
I was young wild boi. I was I was one of those dumb foods
Takes lessons to learn the state experience to learn actually and some people
experience of
Mahal bars or whatever the case so
Exactly the older you get bro the more experience you gain and she like that you learn from your fucking mistakes, you know
Oh my shit. I don't care about much. I don't care about much. I just like to have fun on the internet now
Bob I've been in the streets. I just keep it pushing
Yeah, I mean I would love to make money like and like stream and like get money to where I can pay my bills
But like it's that hasn't happened probably never gonna happen. I got a fucking I got to pay bills, bro
So I'm not gonna like
Wait around like I can't do that. I have to have to work
So if I can't just like, you know what I mean? I can't plus like I yeah
You're part and actually like chopping the editing the videos and shit
That's the only way it can actually work while he's home and you're working
She's chopping up videos can like the videos like I think you might don't like this one
I you know whatever type of videos content you make depend, you know Sam, but you do IRL you say so
It's a little different. I
Mean if I'm gonna like
Let's say like, you know, you know kick they give me KCIP, you know KCIP is
Nah, but I don't I got kick, but I'm not odd to like be small shit
Well, like KC IP is like if you're you get like a verified on kick and they give you like hourly money
Like fucking like a hundred bucks an hour type shit to fucking stream
It'd like give me give me that and I will like clean my act up and I'll stream like just walking around Vegas every day
Instead of my job, I'll quit
You know, I mean these fools get hella money, dude, and it's like I don't have that so like
This is how idiots become rich and when you got a rich idiot should happen. So
Yeah, I mean true
Some of the people that some of the people that stream
That and the people that watch these people. I'm like, why are you why do people watch this?
Well, I'm like and donate to like why would you donate to the you know, I mean, it's I
Give up, you know, I give up
Yeah, I don't donate to everybody, I donate for causes, and if I feel I want to donate
to a specific person for a specific reason, like psyche, then I'll do so.
Well, yeah, I mean that yeah, it's just some people it's just like
I was like this fat guy was locked up. He was like stop what baby pop all day. That's what he said
So what baby pop all day kind of find out he got laced when he was younger with PCP in the last the last
Phrases was those phrases and that shit got stuck in his head
That's all that you probably got you know
Accidentally took it type shit, you know
like he be talking to you, he'll talk to you in sign language and I'll be like, oh well he's immediately like
then the story came out, what happened to her because people knew him in the streets
he got laced with PCP when he was younger
and he talks with sign language but all he says is
are they so what?
Yeah, so you got laced with somebody fucking like they smoked this shit at homey
and they smoked it all crazy and got fucked up, right?
Yup, and those are the last phrases that he must have said because that shit got stuck in his head
That's all bad dude, yeah
Well, I'm out in Vegas, bro. I see I see hella people like homeless people that are all cracked out like
Yeah, I heard they cleaned that up pretty good. And there was actually a news article
How how how they clean up the arm the homeless like I don't say clean it up
I say let's relocate them people if they want to be homeless listen to what it's given a section go stroll through
They every day make sure nobody's hurt. Nobody's home. There's no fight going on
Whatever they're homeless. They can't afford
Yeah, because there's like this. Yeah. What about every say give give a portion like I only be homeless in this section of the city go over there
Yeah, there was this one wash that they kicked a bunch of people out that were living there because they have to like do like work
construction on the on the wash like the fucking
so they kicked a bunch of people out, but it's like if it was me man if you're homeless because you're fucking
You're fucking tweaker. You're doing meth. You're smoking fucking meth. You're fucking tweaker
Like it I can understand it, but here's the thing. I you know, I'm an ex tweaker from years ago or whatever
I've done met. I've been out here Vegas five years. I've done that multiple times out here
I've done the Vegas math it sucks
Like fucking I can't believe people like shoot because there's salvation army. There's a place that you can go
But you have to like, you know stay clean three days
salvation will be helping but
Man, let's stay away from hard drugs. I'm proud that you say you off that God bless because those are those are those are the ones
Those are the ones. Yeah, it's all that. It's all I said
Back when I was this back when I was in my 30s, bro
I feel like God bless you you survivor because I just smoke weed and I don't want to do nothing else from nothing else
I am good when I was in my like my my young 30s and shit cuz I'm 39
But yeah, I fucking in my 20s like fucking I see you growing up in the project
You see like the destruction of drugs. I used to look at people like oh my god. This is a cracker
Yeah, crack is cracks all bad, too. I've never done a crack in my life. Oh, this is a coke head. Look how fast that motherfuckers
But I never got
This motherfucker's rolling down a hill what he's on here. He has
Yeah, I try to stick to the
Yeah, like fucking uh
I don't know you have to
Get you want to get sober and like there's places you can go to sleep and like but you have like work and like go through a
Program to help you like get off the drugs and these people like they would rather live in a tent and smoke fucking meth
Instead of go to the program. That's what I got to say about and
And it's like and it's like fucking and I've done the meth that they that they're talk that they do to choose to do
And it's like this is like cut bunk shit when I was in Cali. I should get fucking
Uncut fucking. I mean you do like a little fucking half inch line, dude
You're awake three days spun off your ass, dude
This shit out here is like cut and I'm like you guys choose to be homeless and smoke meth this meth in Vegas
It's like some of the bonkers shittiest meth I've ever fucking done
No, I mean
And that's it dude, like I could understand I could understand if it was some of the shit
Yeah, you know, it's like I could understand if like, you know, I'm like what
But I mean maybe they I don't know dude, it's like dude
If I had the shit I used to get back in the day and brought it here and sold that shit
Man, I'd be fucking having people knock my door down for this shit dude. They'd be like holy fuck
And I watch my homie my homie because I don't really smoke but you know you lines I wash them
I wash them smoke. I'm like, dude
Well, how many hits you get off that like what four or five off that puddle, you know
Like fucking my shit would last like fucking shit
You'd be going you would just like chill put it away because you'd be like I can't do anymore
And you would still have something, you know for later
I mean
So I actually meth had meth meth had like the outcome of one so I can't relate I can't
None of that. I synced it on the internet, but that's about it
But I can't in person I until it happens. I see it and I can't relate
I feel like I mean I feel like I grew out of it dude. Oh, yeah
I understand what you're saying, but yo shit is crazy each each each section of the United States got their own drug addicts
And they own problems that go with it
Yeah, and everybody's got their own situation. Maybe they're just like I just fuck it
I want to like kill myself with this drug and they like
Well, I mean it's it's it's nothing crazy it's probably what's going on like I don't know people like everybody's got a different like you know lifestyle like
So they like circumstances like why let's get to that. Yeah, people go to heart big up go to hard lives
We end up, you know, they end up referring to drugs just to get out of existence. Like I won't yeah. Yeah
Exactly. Yeah, like people like there's been there's people I hear that I
Just that it came out here
one of my homies that I know he's an older guy too. He's like 60 dude and he's a tweaker and shit and he's like
Retired on disability, whatever he gets monthly money. He's homeless
Because he gambles like he takes
Anybody got the link can you drop the link in the chat anybody else could come up
Not to say we're not having a good conversation. I'm just saying I like I have yeah, I'm just I'm just talking dude
You know, I'm preparing people remember that
You can always come up ahead and drift this conversation somewhere. We I'm a conversationist. I could talk to you about anything
Let's talk. Yeah. Yeah
We are gambling addiction gambling addiction is real. Do you motherfuckers come out here like combination is a bad one, too
Is that then you know if you are gambling addicted? I'm drunk
Oh my god, it's weaker or whatever dude like fucking yeah, yeah, that's three. That's three like that's a combo
You go you're gambling you're addicted to gambling your dick. It's drugs. That's bad right there
So you need a gamble to make your money to get your drugs
Well, that's what I'm saying when I'm one of these bulls I know like I've monthly money from the government for being retired
Homeless and fucking cuz he couldn't stop going like gambling like he spends his whole like thousand twelve hundred dollars
At the casino every month, and he's like oh, I'm like his name is Mike. I'm like dude Mike fucking stop
You know, I mean I'd like stop you I would let you like like live with me, dude
Because you have like a secure income
Like we could be roommates dude, but like he like he has to gamble. He's a gamble holic or whatever like he's addicted
And he's like homeless because of that dude. I'm like, dude, you can't stay here. Like I can't fucking
Gamble I gamble but I'm not all crazy about it because I fucking uh, I need to listen
I need to find out I need to find out like the way
I want to like the casinos are ripping fucking people off, right? I want to fucking I want to rip them off like you know
I mean next time I come there
I'm gonna find out this the solution to fucking get my money back that you guys have you know type shit. That's what I say
Go in as a retard. That's what I say. I
Mean no disrespect to nobody but go in the look of the little whatever, you know and
Like you get lucky and you got somebody helping you walk in you
I just need I need a better than you do get it get it. You're smarter than the usual person
I need better. I don't know better better psychic powers, dude
I need to see into the future like 10 seconds
Maybe 15 and I could fucking know the palm palm back of your head and then
You be I can do that
They go past I know that the roulette ball is gonna land on fucking nine red
10 seconds before it does maybe maybe 15 seconds before bro. I'll fucking bet my life
You know my fucking everything
You know
Oh, I see this I see that oh the
It's like an orb. It's like a glass orb. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, one of those like the um
That was it she called I'm not reading chat. I'm trying to oh wait. Oh, yeah, let's see the channels
Oh shit chat. What up chat? Shout out to the chat. Yeah, I already know when I say this is over
Shout out to be the kitty gang. He man CB
We got up in here. We got mojo fatal. You're ready
Shorty
You got Brian King
All right, let me see what they saying now marshy for the box sister face. All right
it was just one of the
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. Don't worry people. He's back at one crystal ball. Is that what it is?
Oh, that's what it's just a crystal ball. Yeah, there you go. Yeah
Sikey me one of those crystal balls
You got the dong and you're gonna do the crystal balls and the meditation
Yes, um, are you ready people Alex come back at one o'clock today
I have to one o'clock tune in because he's gonna go crazy. It's like he's still up. I
Could get a tee that
Yeah, I need a crystal ball, bro
Yeah, crystal. Yeah crystal. Yeah, every time I write crystal that pops up that image up. You're right
crap
She's cool, though. I was just messing with her. She's taking mad personal
Don't joke a little lady. I mean ma'am. I don't know what to call you crystal
But Chris man, you know, so what job you doing actually now I might have missed that
I don't really like I don't like to really say like over on the internet, you know, okay, okay, okay, okay
But yeah, it sucks
I mean maybe yeah, okay, okay, okay, I'll just it I keep it. I hold it down landing the bro
And you can put a live to test me how about that?
See you got to work with the internet the way it works. Yeah, I'm fucking uh, like I said, I might be moving out
I mean, I'm
I've been in Vegas like five years and I'm kind of burnt in and I want to I want to live right near the beach, you know, oh
Florida baby, Florida
Yeah, Florida's got some you know, I there's spots there that are cheaper
You gotta fight the right price it though. Yes
Yeah, cuz there's hella spots just like it's just like Cali in a way, but Cali is like all all expensive
I requested a bunch of IRL streamers when you do you got to hold laptop set up and your selfie sticks and camera fabric
Set up came when I do IRL
Yeah, do you hold? Yeah, I have somebody follow you like a one of those pros
What no I?
We're widening right now. I have an a galaxy s-22 ultra which is great, but I have a
Yeah, I have my setup cuz yeah, I don't know who whappy flanker is
No, no, no
He's a he's a streamer too. He lives out here in Vegas and he's my homie out here and
I have it set up through OBS to where
Like if I get it back signal out in Vegas or something like I but basically I start my stream
On my computer and I could like if I rip like if I have a back connection
I go offline like I'll never go offline like it will go to like a BRB screen without playing like clips
Instead of like, you know, oh my poor if you come up and you in the back. Let me know I'll start yelling psyches
I'll try to get you up. Yeah
Yeah, I have I have that but like that's another thing I have like a really good setup for IRL stream
But like I don't really do it anymore. I stream on rumble
And a lot of times I'm just like sitting on my desktop and doing like podcasts like this
I do the same thing the psych does, you know, I have like people come on and
you could say like a lot more
On rumble because like they won't like ban you
Big shiba rubble too. I got my cow over there ready at all. I got like two videos up. That's about it
I haven't posted up. I'm redowning everything from over here, and I'm gonna repost it over there
Yeah, if you got a rumble bro fucking Chris K Buster dude is
500 videos on my jump, you know I'm saying so I'm gonna take all that I'm gonna bring it over there
Yeah, do it up man. Like rumble. I think
Because YouTube man they they do whatever
the the people that buy ads
Like advertising ads on their videos on videos
They do it, you know, whatever they whatever they want them to do because people will be like, oh wait
I just paid $30,000 to get my ads on these videos
And why don't my watch and some guy like make a fart video or do do do do and they'd like fucking
YouTube, you know, I mean, that's what that's what it is and like rumble
They didn't like that YouTube's all fucking crazy, dude, like they
Good luck, dude trying to like monetize your YouTube channel nowadays
Especially for a live streamer, you know what I mean?
I used to cop watch, you know, if you know about me
It's a cop watch
It'd be be Casper, New York you say just a cop watch
Yeah
Well, I know that there's youtubers out there that literally first amendment auditors. Yeah. Yeah. That's what I was
That's no, I I respect those fools because
Just do it if you want to do that like the it's your it's your good American, right, right to do that
the
Yeah, you know
Yeah, he's like you need anything he's like no, I'm good the lines don't change the lines don't change we all use the same shit
That's why they trip on
Now because there's a lot of people doing it now, so it's drying up
But it's also teaching the government that you know, you're not above not above us
That's when they go to you know, they violate us eventually end up like the LA right right now
Yeah, learn your learn your fucking laws. You're fucking you're a cop, right? You know, you know, it's legal like to record you
Like fucking
Yeah, Riverside accountability
No, it's uh
The guys from like a Victorville Asperia, but that I know who you're talking about right now. I know that channel West Side accountability
No, it's a
Keep saying channels. I'll tell you which one it is
Who's Wappy
Yeah, Wappy Flanker he lives out here in Vegas, and he's my homie like in real life
He's from bow stream. Oh, yeah
With the RV trip Marcy now. I remember now
Fuck is on it. I'm thinking Andy saga that you ever remember what she's saying right now. Yeah
Yeah, you everyone you too right now look up fucking Victorville
Victorville fucking
Audit or whatever dude, and it's a what you say the name. I know it. It's like I tip my tongue
Yeah
He's got he's got a big channel, too. I'd like I forgot about that guy because
Like a couple like I was a year ago with however long I've been bad on YouTube like I lost the main thing I
The main thing I trip on is I lost like people that I subscribe to on my YouTube channel like I
Had to make us, you know, this the channel that I have now is just to chat
But I have subscribed like so many channels that like I forget half the channels that I subscribe to and like I don't watch their shit because YouTube ban me so I
Should shoot that hey man, I should fucking do that shit in Vegas bro be like a was it called like a nightcrawler dude and just like listen to like police scanners
just record cops like a traffic fucking accidents or whatever dude houses
wherever they go and just record them that would be content
They say that again
I was I was I was talking to you the whole time, but would you just say that last part I?
Said fucking I should I should do that like be like a nightcrawler like record cops here in Vegas like get on a police scanner
for like my stream and just like live stream going to like cop like act like car accidents or like, you know
wherever the cops go and just like go to their spots
You get arrested, right? So you know this consequences to get arrested being an auditor, right? Because some cops just can't take it
Yeah, but if I live I here's the thing if I
Every auditor right prepare yourself to get locked up because there's gonna be a cop that could not take you spitting the truth at him
Exactly
Exactly. Yeah, well, I mean the thing the if I did that, you know
I would have to drive and I obviously wouldn't drive because I drink and she liked that when I when I livestreamed
So I wouldn't drive doing that. I wouldn't drive drunk. So I mean the only way that they could trip
Is I don't know I break the law. I'm not wouldn't I would just record them, you know
Yeah, they'll always they'll hound you after that, bro. You'll be known
You'll be known trust me
They will hound you. They see you. They go that motherfucker. Let's make sure he's dirty.
Let's see. What is he doing? They'll look for reasons. Look for reasons. They'll look for that reason.
Trust me. Yeah. Everything. You know I'm recorded, right? You know I'm taking this to the judge.
You know what I'm gonna do, right? All right. You know what I used to tell them?
Or they came to me and were like, you know, listen. Everything you say can and will be used in record alone.
Yeah, I can say they don't like that. They don't like to be filmed you the cops and shit
They're like, why are you filming because I can't how about that?
No, no, no, what you want?
Once you came towards me everything's gonna be used you came towards me. I ain't come towards you
Everything you say can it will be used for the little house keys. What happened?
Yeah, you know protect and serve my ass, dude
I'm scared bro if I come across the cop that's had a bad day his wife just left them whatever dude
I might get shot type shit. You know me
that's it's real pool have that shit fucking come on man
You're the one that went through the goddamn fucking, you know training to you know the classes whatever you have to do to like become a cop
Dude, so fuck you dude. You've made the choice. This is what you get. You know what I mean? That's it
Yeah, there's a lot of a lot of fucking bad fucking cops dude better fucking
Yeah, I think they're above the law all that shit, bro
It's all bad, bro. It's fucking uh
It's fucked up especially in Cali dog LA. I
think that's a lot of reason to do those riots and shit in LA about the fucking
Deportations, I mean, it's I don't think it's in a lot of it's not just that reason dude
I would I mean LA is fucking all the California CHP cops
Like I you know, I've been in Vegas five years do the cops and Cali are like a thousand percent worse than Vegas cops
Do like these cops and Cali fucking
Fucking sweat you dude. Press you. They're fucking looking for anything that they can do to fucking pull you over to fucking
To like they'll search, you know, like they they they break the law they search your car like without a reason
Like they do leave. I mean, it's all bad. Like it's all bad in California. Do cops are all fucking bad, dude corrupt
See a cop in Cali. I'm like, oh shit, dude. Better be cool, dude
Like I even though I have nothing nothing in my car, you know, no no drugs. Nothing. I'm not doing anything
I got a registration as you know
Yeah, they want they that's what they like though. They want you to be all scared and shit
They want you they want to fucking be like a authority or whatever dude, which is bullshit, dude
Like fuck you do my fucking tax money pays your fucking your salary homie
I mean, that's real, dude
Yeah, Brian, I just read your comment. Yeah
Yeah, most right most but there's a few out there that are fucking bad apples, I guess, right?
And you know what like the laws and shit are only getting like more strict as far as like cop
Allowance and shit like that
People had everybody has a camera
Like I remember talking to my my stepdad dude
About back in the 70s and shit he would be like drunk he's like in it
Whatever he was like a teenager in his 20s, whatever and he would fucking be drunk dude and like drive cop a poem over and be like you've been drinking
And they, you know, he's like, no, no.
He's like, yeah, you've been drinking, hey, listen,
you better go straight home type shit, you know?
But nowadays it's like, oh, let me arrest this guy
like fucking for DUI and then make him fucking pay.
Like, because when you have a DUI dude,
it's three years of hell after that.
You have to have SR 22 insurance for three years
on your car if you want to drive.
If you don't have it, then you get...
Pulled over and not have your insurance car insurance, and then that's like it's all you know
Then you get more cop come you know you got to go DUI classes what you have to pay for it's like at the end of the
Day, it's like $5,000 that you have to put in to your DUI
To eventually get it like done and then back to where you have your regular license because I've been through it
I've had a DUI and in California is like the worst state to fucking go through a DUI dude
That's why I don't fucking drink and drive you
Like I won't even have one beer and drive you because I have bad luck with cops and shit like that
I'll fucking drink like a 24 ounce beer and like I'm cool
I've only had you know and dry all like I'll pull out of my driveway and a couple is like whoop whoop pull me over
You know, that's my luck. So it's like I don't even risk it. It's not worth it. I'm not getting the DUI ever again
I'll pay for an uber, you know or a lift to fucking give me a ride if I have to go somewhere type shit once I'm drinking
Yeah, that's I mean, that's
Not only that like fucking Vegas like fucking there are so many drunk drivers like car accidents like
Nevada
Clark County, Nevada like Southern Nevada Vegas is like one of the like most expensive car insurance
Rates like in the country
And it's like I see this shit when I drive
I'm like I see accidents all the time like I just like well they just had an accident like the airbags just deployed the chicks crying
Holy shit, you know what I mean? It's like I like on a daily basis like people don't know how to drive out here
And it's like don't wonder the car insurance out here if you live here is that much because they don't want to even like cover you because like it's like
Yeah
Yeah, I mean, I agree Brian
Depends where you live too, man, you know depends if it's like a
I don't want to get into politics, you know, I mean like Republican and Democratic state
You know people like have different views on shit like that
Yeah
I mean, it's I actually because I mean I get sweated
You know, I'll be doing like, you know in a 35 I'll be doing like maybe 45 dude
And then a cop just I see a cop pass a copy comes comes up behind my ass right on my ass dude
Read my plates run on my shit, right?
And I'm like, you know, I know that I have insurance registration. Everything's fine like and uh, I'm like this guy's sweating me
Dude, I just a block away around the corner dude. I just seen this guy in the corner fucking like
Naked like smoking fucking crack dude, and you got you want to like sweat me like turn around dude
The guy's over here like fucking like walking across the street
In traffic dude like smoking a crack pipe, and then you're pulling you trying to get a pull me over
You know what I mean? I got pulled over dude because I have a car that's not a fucking Cadillac
And I put a I scraped off the emblem that's on there and I put a Cadillac emblem on there, right?
I got pulled over because the cop was like, oh, I wanted to be I read your ran your plates and it came back
You know, this isn't a Cadillac. I'm like, yeah, I know
Like it's obviously not a Cadillac. He's like, oh, it's not maybe when it's stolen car
No, no, no, just the reason like I gave them a reason to pull me over so like literally after that
They'd like they searched my car. They've been you know, put your hands on the hood and stand there or whatever dude
Because my passenger side back window. He's like roll your back window down
Passure or driver side back window. I'm like it doesn't it doesn't work like it doesn't roll down
So he thought I was like lying like giving him a hard time and shit so he fucking you know
He's like can you step out of the vehicle?
And all this shit. I was like, yeah, yes, sir, you know, he's like can you stand in front of my car?
And they like searched my car thought I had drugs or whatever. I'm like, nah, dude. I'm just going to work, dude
He's like, yeah, sorry, you know, let's let you all good. Let you on your way
Like, you know, they have a cat I put a Cadillac emblem as a joke, you know, it's not a cat
He did it's a beater. My car is a little buster car, dude
So like literally like that later that night I
Fucking I took it off and I put the original emblem back on the car dude because I don't want to get
like sweated like I want to just like
Yeah, and everybody was like fuck that why would just leave it on dude every time he did it, but like you know, I mean I'm
I'm not trying to like rebel. I'm trying to like
Conformed I guess in a way conformed you because I don't want to get sweated bro. I've been to jail prison
I've been on fuck, you know, I got multiple felonies on my record. Do cops see all that shit, dude
Like I don't want to fucking like give them a hard time
I'm done dude like fucking if you get if you got I can't have a caddy emblem on my fucking
Buster mobile then so be it dude. You know me
But yeah, they have like out here. They have like the cop cars
I have automatic cameras that just zoom in on your license plate and run it like without them even typing it in
The cops get behind me
Run my shit dude, and then I have these fools they get pulled over out here like they don't have
Insurance car insurance
Their registration suspended, you know, that's why they get pulled over and then they're drunk or whatever it is
And they go you've been drinking dude, you know
But yeah, like dude, it's not
Vegas is like these cops are like our pussies compared to like Cali cops you Cali cops are like
Like way way more like like hardcore dude
Because they had like California select
They probably get paid more the cops probably get paid more in Cali in LA, San Bernardino, whatever do you Orange County?
So they need to have a quota and I know they have a quota to in Vegas
But they have a quota that they need to meet as far as writing tickets
Monthly so they have to like you know the sergeant is the sergeant of police department like hey
You know, we need to get 500 ticket or whatever whatever amount you these guys need to start pulling people over for like speed write them speeding tickets and shit
You know because there's been times, you know that I've got like a speeding ticket and then other times where the cop is like
Let's you go but other times he's like he's like there's no way you can talk your way out of this because he's like
I need to get this on my like under my belt to get my fucking quota done for this month and that's facts, dude
That's what they do
So don't you know, don't try not to speed try not to give them a reason to play over and
That's the main thing don't don't ride dirty. Don't have to make sure you have car insurance
make sure you're fucking everything's legit on your plates your registration and
that's what I do and
Yeah, and I've had cops. I mean I drive it kind of drive a little bit out here
And it's like I see cops just like fucking getting behind me, dude. I was like, oh, yeah
It run on my shit. Let me see here. Are you gonna pull me over like I mean and they don't they just like they
Did they pull aside go go ahead of me like they're like, oh, there's nothing we could pull this guy over for
You know
So I mean that's that's it. I'm just talking chat. What's up?
Yeah, that's you cheat to Chong is like one of my favorite all-time movies, dude
That's the part where they were he pulls over and they after they got done smoking that joint
And he's like am I driving okay, and then Chong's like I think we're part man
They like he's like oh man never had no stuff like that before man. That's some heavy shit, man
That's some heavy shit. He's like hey mellow out man
mellow out
He's like just go oh
Oh
He's like, wait, no, he's like, come on now.
Take these, take these.
And he takes them.
He's like, wait, no, don't take those.
He's like, what do you mean don't take those?
I already took them.
He's like, oh, ho, ho, ho.
You just took the most acid I've ever seen.
He's like, I never had no acid before, man.
It's gonna make me die, man.
He's like, I can't breathe.
I can't breathe.
That's mellow.
There, feel better.
He's like, oh man, how long is this shit last man?
He's like, hey man, you better move man. I think we're on the wrong street then the cops come up behind him
Excuse me, sir. Can I see your registration? He's like my registry. It's back there on the license, but
Hey, man, am I driving okay?
Yeah, I, if you guys ever watch my rumble when I do stream,
I get on a like monkey app and I play, I play characters.
I literally like, I'll play characters to the people
that I talk to and yeah, it's content.
Yeah.
And I do a lot of quote. I could do a lot of movie quotes. I could be I could be an actor
I need I need to like get somehow get into that because I could do whatever whatever the
Director wants me to do or how they want me to act I can do it like a guy guy could play anything
If you get you know, I say like I said if you watch my rumble dude, I'm not trying to promote my channel on rumble
But you know what I mean? Like that's what I do sometimes
On I you know random people a monkey at monkey app is like you join people in like Iran
It's a random person like I'll literally put a beanie on
With some fucking loaks some like shades on and shit and be like hey
What's up play like a fucking cholo and shit be like I just got popped. I I just got popped in my knee
Yeah, I was I'll make up a story like I just got home to my house and I'll tell him like some story
They're like, oh man, you need to get to the hospital and all this shit. Yeah, I do that. I do it
or like i'll be sitting there dude and i'll just like play it off like my wife's in the kitchen
i'll be like hey keisha no hey don't burn my fucking bacon this time but no man i kind of like you
know hey just i don't want it crispy like i'm talking to somebody in another room there's
like nobody there but the people that just came in came into the uh the monkey app channel they're
like oh man this will yell at his wife right now or whatever you know i mean
yeah i do i do i do like some crazy shit on there it's con i mean i think it's content
Have like other ideas. I want to do on there, but I don't want to get like it like a trouble. I guess I'm yet to get banned, dude
Yeah, I think the people that run monkey app or just like they see me on there. There's like damn that shit's funny, bro
like
And I'll get on there and I'll come across some fool that's like fucking you could tell he's like, you know jacking off
on cam i'm like i'll wait i'm like hey right this day this is it get his ip get his ip yeah this is the same guy from before
like i act i'd like yeah i'm from i'm from uh monkey incorporated uh we've been following your channel i play
like i'm like uh monkey you're like a like a bed and i've been watching them because like some people get on monkey
up and they're like they're like jacking off dude like to like little kids
Right, so I'm like, yeah, you you know, I'm like you're gonna get it
You're gonna get a temporary ban or we got your IP address
We know what you're doing on this on this platform
You know, it's not allowed and the police will be informed. Did I say all that shit? Yeah
Can I type in chat
I mean, just go to rumble.com and then go to the search.
It's Chris K. Buster.
It's it with no spaces.
Chris K. Buster, I mean.
Yeah, Chris K. Buster, like with no spaces.
Yeah, I remember I remember when I got beat up by the midget. Yeah
See that's that's what I was talking to that fool was it easy
See that's what I do when I do IRL out here in Vegas like I get I get fucking too drunk and
I trip on people because I think that they're fucking mad dog. I mean shit and fucking ain't I'm getting in fights and
Yeah
Text my text wappy like on a daily basis. Yeah, he's my homie, bro
I'm just afraid to like because I'm on my phone, bro
I'm afraid like minimize and put the link in chat of my rumble because I might it might kick me off
So just rumble.com
forward slash user
I don't know just Chris K. Buster Chris K. Buster and
there's an icon of like a
lion
Yeah, check it out it because I can't I got banned on YouTube and
I have a kick, but I don't really stream on it. I'm like saving my kick. I don't know why
No, I'm not on right now because my desktop
hard drive on my computer is like dead dying and
I need to get another hard drive and I haven't got one yet
I need to like literally reinstall windows on my computer. So I'm like on my phone
right now
But I'm like I literally have my computer on right now and I'm working on maybe
Reinstalling the windows on a different hard drive that I have already, but I'm like
Yeah
Yeah, I used to be live a lot more than I am now.
Like I said, my hard drive is going on my computer.
I could go live from my phone.
I'm just right now, I'm in Sykes shit right now.
I might actually later.
I might go live just from my phone.
But yeah, I like to do panels.
Like psych like same thing psyched us, but I have like a different like type of people
It's about it
Well, yeah, I don't really I gave up man I
give up on trying to
You know quote-unquote make it screaming on the internet I gave up because I see people that
the people that watch
Some of the people that live stream. I'm like, I cannot believe people are what like this guy's got what six thousand views and
Like I'm watching I'm watching the stream. I'm like this guy is like
You know, I don't want to get too vulgar with what I you know, but he's like
It's I mean is it like do I have to act like this to get to get viewers to like make it streaming?
And it's like I give up
Type shit. So it's like, you know, I don't focus on it. There's, you know, some people
Focus on trying to like stream to like, you know, get get money
And I'm like done like I don't care
Like I I I've moved on and uh, people want to watch me great if not like and if you don't like me
I don't care. I'm not trying to like please anybody like that's it
Like I mean, I don't even I don't have to like even uh
Come on panels, you know, you guys you guys don't even know who I am, right? Like I'm out. I'm just you know
And then I go on the you know these forums and I see like stuff that people clip and put on the forums and I'm like
Why would you put that on there? Like it's not even funny the guys like you know
Not funny and it's like I've done so much more stuff that's like
way like better content and like nobody,
I don't know if they didn't see it, you know what I mean?
So I was just like, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, what's your name?
Damn, I mean, 110,000 those starting off is really good.
Yeah, I hear that. I mean, I hear you, dude.
Yeah, I think with me, like, you know, especially like when I do IRL, like maybe my
I got to, like, just not drink or just no one, no one to, like, stop.
Because I, like, I over drink and I get, like, drunk and
You know, I always like get into like something dude, which is content. I go he's get into something which is content right click that gets clipped
but I
Can't you know, that's not gonna be I can't do that all the time
You know, and if I want to be persistent and like fucking have like viewers that like, you know, yeah, I get it
I know you know, dude. It's just like fuck
Yeah, he's grinded dude 110k dude fuck like especially YouTube
I can't stream on there anymore, like I'm banned.
If I made, you know, the channel that I have now,
if I made another channel and started getting big,
they would probably know or whatever it is.
So I'm gonna be, I can't do it.
Yeah, Reddit, I'm not trying to do anything, dude.
Yeah, I mean, you know when people watch a live stream
At least, you know, you know, I know you guys know what IP2 is a
Lot of my viewers like they
They they call they'll call like where you're at they'll find your location. They'll call they'll get you kicked out
If they do donate they'll donate a racist song over the TTS where like, you know
It's like super racist to where like, you know people will try to like
fight you or like, you know, she like that. That's what that's how it is. Uh,
Yeah.
Which I'm not, I'm not like scared. I'm not, I don't care, dude. I've only had a few donations that were like that
Um
But I'm not you know a lot of people will they'll hear that racist don't know and
They'll like run away and like out of the store and like you know run away. I would just stand there. I
mean
Because if you cancel the don't know then you're a scammer right
You're like a streamer like somebody donated to pay play that song
I would just let it let it play through and if fucking if I get if I get beat up and somebody attacks me then so be it
That's what I think
I mean obviously I'm gonna try to defend myself or whatever dude, but yeah, I mean you're you're fucking asking for it
You know, you're you're fucking around dude. You're gonna find out I
Mean that's it you're gonna let somebody donate a song that's like racist in front of like, you know other people
They're gonna fucking trip on you then
That's it
I don't know, I mean.
YouTube is,
like I would say the strictest one.
YouTube and Twitch are like the strictest as far as,
you know, like striking your channel
or like, you know, banning you for shit.
So that's why that's why am I still on psych shit right now, or is this just did he the industry?
I even know if sex sites not even live anymore
Sacks not live where this is just stream yard or what's going on here, dude
Is psych still streaming me or did he go offline?
Okay, cool. Like I said, like, you know, obviously, I know that if psych is like still live,
if psych is still live, like, I, you know, I have to watch what I say.
Yeah, I have to watch what I say because I it's like I have you know, he's never done me wrong
I'm not gonna like you know intentionally fucking shit up dude. That's cuz he's you know in a way. He's the homie dude, so I
Just I have to like, you know, depend
I have to bite my tongue when I know that somebody's like
Streaming on YouTube or whatever. I know I know that I know their terms of service
Okay, I could get into the whole the whole thing about that
Crazy, bro
And that you know YouTube like the
You know everybody you know everybody needs like to get money dude YouTube is Google dude, right?
They're like one of the biggest like, you know companies in the world and
You know
They need you know average like I said advertisers
When you buy a cell phone, dude, an iPhone, a Galaxy phone, I mean, it comes like pre-installed with YouTube app on the phone, dude.
Everybody has YouTube. Everybody knows what YouTube is. And like they are like, you know, they, at the end of the day, they get so much like ad revenue or like whatever, dude, like money from, you know, the Internet.
They they they don't care if they like banned somebody or whatever dude. You're just like it doesn't matter how big your channel is
You know and that this is fat, you know, it's facts dude, and I get it
I wish I could be YouTube CEO dude and just be chilling a
Right on the beach boy with a like a fucking pina colada, dude
Sitting watching fucking the sailboats out on the ocean, dude
Because that's what the YouTube CEO is doing, bro. You know, I mean so I gotta give them, you know
That's what you need to do. You need to be like that. You need to be like that because like, you know
Yeah
Yeah, I know it's like to sleep probably and like, you know passed out and like and I'm still here
I'm about to leave though and
I know I might go live on my rumble or something dude
Long story, but yeah, but I'd like I'm trying to like fix my computer
So I do go live it'll be on my phone, which is gonna be up like a buster stream from my phone
But it is what it is
Yeah, he's somebody's trying to join the stream yard. I don't I can't invite you because I don't
Have like the you know
I just you know, I get carried away when I talk about shit dude
And I'm trying to like and I don't think anything I say is wrong like I'm trying to like a look at the other side
Of like how somebody can argue is what I say like everything I say about YouTube. I mean, it's it's accurate
And I'm not I'm not like making fun of it or whatever dude. It's like
You know at the end of the day I it was my fault that YouTube, you know banned my channel, dude, you know, I should have
Done this I should have done that, you know
So and I shouldn't have done that I should have said, you know, I
Wish everybody that's
Trying to make it on YouTube. I wish them like the best dude, and I'm trying to like find algorithm
Because some of the people some of the people that make big like I mean make videos. I
Mean people people that make videos and upload them to YouTube are some of the biggest youtubers, dude
Like they don't even live stream, you know, I mean it's like I need to do that because I could edit videos all day
Anyways
I would do I would say
The live streaming dude on YouTube is you know if you can make it live streaming on YouTube dude
That's probably the one of the hardest things to do
But if you can make videos dude like you know vlogs like people make videos and upload videos and they get views
You know that way you know that you're not going to be
You're not gonna upload anything that's gonna get you in trouble dude
Uh
Yeah, I mean the panel link is there dude, but uh unless um psych
A lot like he's asleep right and let's see fucking wakes up. It's like oh this guy's backstage and lets you on
Then you're just gonna sit backstage
I
Know I know dude I already know
If you guys know, if you guys know who Roman Atwood is, right, he, uh, you know, he used to make a lot of prank videos with Tali
Back in the day and now he does does blogs
Which is just like him and his family at his house
I mean, I haven't watched his videos. Listen, I haven't watched his videos for like years
but uh
I know that he does blogs
Of him and his house
Just walking. He's like, hey guys, what's up? Like walking around his house. Like here's my kids. Here's my wife
He used to get copyright striked for wearing like emblems like Nike on the shirts or
Like any brand name of stuff
Mountain Dew Coke can sitting on his counter or
Fucking anything YouTube cuz he I mean he gets like fucking a million views per video
So he like if you watch like a lot of his shit like he'll have to he like takes like put duct tape
And that's why he made his own clothing, you know company called smile more
So he sells shirts called smile more shirts clothes and he's making a killing dude
You know, he basically put it back to back on YouTube's ass like oh you're gonna try to like trip on me
I'll make my own
Stuff that I can that's legal to have on you know, so that's how that's how YouTube does it
Got to give him props dude
So he all he wears in his whole family all they wear all the time is like smile more
Which is his own brand which cannot be copyrighted copyrighted or like anything about you know I mean and
So I got to give him mad respect about that like you know every time he probably goes grocery shopping
He can't show brand names of like anything or like he'll get in trouble type shit
That I mean that's what you got to do if you're you know me
That's what it is smile. I'm already rolling out with bro. I
Gotta give a mad I gotta give a mad respect dude. He made it. He fucking made it on on YouTube
Yeah, Brian, exactly.
Yeah, it's not YouTube's fault, but what YouTube like,
the people that put the strikes are like,
I don't want this guy to like monetize or profit
from talking down on or fucking representing my brand,
like their brand.
So that's why they do it, which I get it.
Once you get as big as Roman out with though, like yeah, that's when YouTube is like watching you
Everyday people that YouTube Google are watching his as they upload
You know I mean and I like they're making sure that there's nothing that anybody can say about it
You know
Because I mean, there's a hell of videos out there with people with like brand name shirts on dude that have millions of views on YouTube, right?
But they gave him a hard time because he's making bank, dude. I mean, what I mean, look it up. How much does he make a month on YouTube, dude?
Rolling out, you know what I mean? Millions?
Know in a way. It's the same as TV dude
like television like if you look a
TV movies and shit, I
Mean the most of people the actors and shit. They're not wearing. I mean if they are they're getting sponsored
They're not wearing brand-name stuff like on TV and like movies
Is that a lot of like there's no emblems, you know, I mean think about it think about every movie, you know
Movie like newer movie you've seen dude. There's really like nothing
You know, there's no like imp like no nothing. They just were like, you know
If there is they they have it off or like whatever and if there is
If there is like fucking
Can a Pepsi or something like that then like
Or like if they're driving a car and it's a Chevy or a Ford or a Dodge whatever car
like they
The company like told them that they're like we're making a movie over here
You know if you guys want to offer a car we can use we'll use it our movie like you know free of charge like oh
Yeah, here's like what do you guys need?
You guys gonna like show our cars in the movie like our Chevy's our Ford's in your movie
Like here's a free car to use in your movie
Like you know I mean and like is it okay?
We use the in the Chevy emblem in the movie like look at some movies dude. They like the emblems on the cars aren't there
You know, but if they if it is there then like you know, they're allowing it
Yeah
the company is like the company in a way is sponsoring the movie by letting you use,
you know, they're not going to sue you, right? By using Chevy in the movie or fucking, you know,
having a can of Pepsi, like it's advertising the company, right? They're like, yeah, here's some
Pepsi. And I always wondered about that because, you know, in Wayne's world, where they're like,
you know, I don't want to sell out or whatever. And then like, they go to this whole scene like,
Wayne's like, you know, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I don't, I'm not that type to sell out, but I'm so thirsty right now.
And he like drinks a Pepsi. He's like, oh, this is a good choice to drink.
And it's like Pepsi, like the choice of the next generation.
And it goes to Garth and he's like wearing Reebok.
He's like full Reebok gear.
He's like, yeah, man, I just never understood, you know, selling out to a company or whatever.
You know, it's just something I wouldn't do.
And he's like, oh, I got a headache.
And he's like, you know, take these, you know, it's like ad bill.
You know little small different so they like they actually had those people that I don't know if you guys don't talk
But they're like advertising it but at the same time talking about not advertising Wayne Wayne's world, dude
Yeah, Mr. Beast dude
I need I never really I don't watch mr. Beast
Hear about him. He's on Amazon now, I guess which I have Amazon Prime
But yeah, I mean hats off to him bro like oh the only video that I remember because I have watched a few videos
The only one that I that I use that watch that I liked
He went to some like somebody somewhere has an underground
like fallout shelter
Or like a nuclear war and it's like literally like fucking was it 20 floors?
Like they grow their own plants their own food
Like this like 20 love like 20 floors and he like he went down there and like lived there for 20 day
Like a cup like a week or whatever was and I was like damn dude. That's crazy
Like there's like, you know somebody that has that like he went in there and like stayed down there
And I thought that was really cool like whoever's like running that I think that's a really cool idea like
There's like a nuclear war and you got to go into a fallout shelter
These guys have like 20 floors deep of fucking they can live like like forever
They're like growing plants care like food
They have like all the shit they're getting electricity from like however they do it like I forget the whole the whole scenario
But that was one of the videos I was like down that's dope
Like I hope that like, you know other platforms like kick rumble
Like I hope that they you know get bigger dude
But then you have you know like say mr. Beast dude like he's not gonna leave YouTube
What I'm saying is like, you know, you have to like get people you have to like pay them money to like switch platforms
Like big streamers like big I'm start talking about streamers and
Then if they do like the platform the people that the platform knows that like
this big youtuber is
Switching the platform like all the viewers what are gonna know about it and like that that's gonna bring though those viewers to that platform also
Which will make it like more popular
You know, I mean
So that's how it works YouTube is like cornered the cornered the market on like videos and
Life like live streaming is still like I mean, that's the biggest platform for live-streaming. I mean in twitch
Even you know, even when kick came out all the big twitch streamers like they
Think they were offered like you know a kick was like hey, dude. We'll give you like some money like you know to switch the kick from twitch
and they're like
They're like no we're good because they they're good if you're if you're a kick the kicks a twist rumor
You're getting 10k
Views and you're getting like subs like you know you have like a sub goal
Let you know they have a sub goal of like 900
Of a thousand, you know and you get like half that done in one stream to three. I mean you're getting hella money regardless
So they're like, you know, they have viewers
That on the platform already. So they're like, you know, maybe we would we could move the kick from twitch
But they're like why like we're doing fine on this but you know this platform that we're currently on
There's there's a few that there's few like these smaller like streamers from twitch that we kick kick kick about
They they went to kick and they're still doing good on kick
But like the big the big twitch streamers like you know, they're like
You know, they they don't want to like lose their audience that they have on the platform they're currently on I mean, that's it
That's it
Yeah, there's been a lot that I think I know that I think I'm on top of my head, but there's been a lot of people that have
Like quit YouTube because
YouTube, you know after like 10 15 years
You know thousands of videos that they had uploaded their channel
Suddenly they're YouTube decided to remove all these videos after like 15 years
You know what I mean, it's like they're like what?
Like I took you 15 years, you know, I mean
There's been people that are just like well, you know, I'm yeah, I'm off the internet. See you guys later, you know
And they're like they like literally shut their channel down on YouTube
There's like all I'm done on this platform or way, you know, whatever
Which I mean in a way that does that make sense like 15 years, dude
You're removing videos after 15 years, you know, it's like but for like, you know, and then to get all the YouTube
To reverse it or like fight it is like it's not nothing like they're like you can't do nothing
It's like it's it final decision like fucking you can't email them
You can't fucking get a hold of anybody YouTube to like, you know fight your you know fight your case
And it's like, you know at the end of the day, they don't give a fuck
There's so many other people out there that are like making them money that like they're like this you're like an ant
In a fucking, you know, you know in a on a planet
You know, like there's this like oh, whatever do they what oh, what'd you say Jimmy?
Oh, yeah, this guy what there's issues with all that. Just just remove his videos. Anyways, hey Susie
Yeah, what we have for lunch. Yeah. Oh, yeah, let's have sushi at the bar. That's how quick they do it
They there's you know, the the the CEO or the the the the
Supervisors like they're like hey, hey, hey Bill
This guy over here has got some you know issues with somebody with these videos. I mean, it's 15 years old
I mean, what should we do? Hey, just you know anything about a listen. I'm trying to talk to Susie over here
Just a just remove the videos
Go get away go go by the way Susie. Yeah. Oh, yeah, I like your cleavage Susie. Hey
Yeah, oh
Yeah, you got you want to go to lunch or whatever. That's how fast they do it and they they like they don't get I mean
That's fast and they don't care
Like, I'm pretty sure that's the way they make decisions over there
And it's like you just like ruined
somebody's life by
Removing all those videos or whatever whatever the whatever the situation and it happens that quack but that quick
Like on their end, you know what I mean?
And they're just like they'd like they don't care at the end of the day, you know, they don't care. Well, like, you know
of the
death of the death of the death of the death of the death of the death of the death of the death of the death of the death of the death of the
the way I look at it.
You wanna be that guy that makes those choices, dude.
That's what people, that's what I wanna be.
I wanna be the CEO of YouTube, dude,
and make the choices like that
and just like not care about it
to where like I could just say fuck you to everybody
and still have enough money to like live my life
and be fine regardless of what anybody fucking says, dude.
That's the goal.
That's what I think.
When you when you get that when you get that fucking uh
Money did money is money makes the world turn dude
Like if you you know people to say that money doesn't buy happiness or fucking bullshit the money fucking
buys you whatever you fucking wanted
If you have enough money, dude, you can fucking do what you want, dude
Sorry, let me read the chat. I don't know what you're going to say, but...
Brian, you're going to have to like let me know about those YouTube chats,
do live chats with YouTube moderators, where and how.
Like, Brian, let me know, because I will say sorry for my previous...
Getting banned on YouTube and like
Like they don't let me make a channel like I make one dude and they ban it
They know who I am and they ban my YouTube so that when I have now
It's just for chatting dude, but if YouTube is like, okay, yeah, you can like get subs like I will stream on YouTube
But it's like I'm not gonna waste my time and gain a bunch of subs and be like they're gonna have YouTube
Oh, yeah, this is the same asshole that we banned before again out and
Then it's like lose it dude. Like that, you know, it's like fucking you build an audience you build a subscription base
And if they just ban you fucking, you know
Because you're like been bad your your bad ban evasion is that what it's called your your vote, you know
You know me then it's like I'm not gonna stream on your platform like I'm done. I move on to the next platform
Like that's the only choice you have
Uh, like Charlie yeah, I mean give me a second here
Yo, KZ, uh, he fell asleep bro, and I'm still here
I'm all leave dude
Oh yeah, I'm like still here, like you fell asleep
and I'm like still here.
Like if the link to join or whatever,
if you know, you'll be backstage
because I can't let you, you know,
Psyche has to like let you in.
The Streamer link, the Streamer link,
he has to use the man.
He's the only one that can do it
unless he has somebody else modded.
Which I used to have somebody else modded, but then this guy
Got like super blackout drunk and started fucking like putting people backstage on
my stream
That I'm like dude. Why let him talk just cuz you guys have different opinions
He had a different opinion, you know, I said I had unmod them so I don't have a
But yeah, sometimes I get drunk and I'm like a dude like I want a mod on my stream yard
To like, you know, sometimes I don't see somebody backstage and this guy will like he used to like let him come on
He's like, you know, help me modernize it
Yeah, like once a YouTube YouTube is Google dude Google is YouTube like they're the same. They're the same and
Google is like
Is is the end of Google is the Internet dude? You can't there's no way the Google's like
Runs this shit, dude, you know
So
see that's you want to be you want to be like the
You want to be the boss, dude? I mean that's what I that's what I think I'm gonna be the boss, bro
of the
the
Yeah, I'm gonna like leave to dude. So sorry guys. You guys are gonna look at a black screen
Until a psych wakes up, I guess
I'm gonna try to like fuck around my desktop computer, I guess
Like waiting to get paid I just need to get a hard drive I'm gonna get a terabyte SSD
Like a Samsung or Western digital and just reinstall windows
Yeah, that's what it is it like freezes and I'm actually on my desktop right now, which is crazy
Does it okay, I didn't know I did that after that after there's nobody on panel all right
Kate Kate Kate Kate
Yeah
I don't even know who it is dude. It's hard to like just do a reading on some random person that you heard by their name on the internet I
Would say that come up and come up or a mic up and talk to me, but you know you can't
Kate
Well, okay, never find the love or if a female filament out of out of life Kate Kate give me a second Kate
well here the reason there's something going on there's a reason why hold on dude
uh charlie
i'm trying to think but what does she uh
Try to send me vibes I get like I'm trying to think this is kind of dumb dude
They say send vibes over of my fucking over this shit, but a lot of times I have to see
Lot of times I have to like I have to see the person
Yeah, well, I can't listen you say that that's not how I do it
What do you say like put three cards out and I have to do the whole thing
I don't I don't do it half-assed
Then let me just try it. Let me try it. Let me try it
Miss it, let me try I'll do one on Kate
Is she a
Is she like are you talking to her right now Charlie
Kate if you are like ask her ask her how many times to shuffle the cards
Oh, yeah two or three
Yeah, two or three dude because five is gonna mess me up
It seems like the second.
Okay, that's crazy. Oh, it's accurate. Tell me if uh
No, I mean she uh, she's uh, she's she's like somebody
She'd like somebody and right now she's got that she likes
But she has like her dad dude her dad her father
Her father if he's still alive
what is up with her father did
So, okay, what's up like she did her dad pass away
Where's her dad
Are you gonna be
Okay, well, I don't know what I don't know what the deal is, but I mean, I'm what it's saying is like her fucking dad
It's like in charge somebody her dad is in charge
And then again like
Did um
Well, I mean, I don't know why I know this but like did she used to like her daddy's like take when she was young
That all she is when she was like youngest shit her daddy's like carry her on her shoulder on her on his shoulders
And she used to like she's like back in the day. She's like when when she was young when she's like a little I don't hold
And her dad
Her dad and then her dad again over here
Did I don't know if she has a
This this K chick I don't know if she's seeing like does she have a kid does she like a single mom?
If not, then it's
Then there's something else there with with her mom or something, but yeah, her dad
Like instilled in her dude like fucking something crazy when she was younger and I don't know
I don't know if she has like brothers the Kate has brothers or sisters like
That that her dad likes three brothers or I'm not three but her her and two other people
Brothers or sisters. There's three people that her dad
Like that fucking you know like her brothers and shit like fucking her dad had and her dad was like
Oh, like her dad was like fuck. I don't know what he did
But like what what is what is up with her real her real dad back when she was younger?
To okay
Yeah, three other people
But I don't know why you got you guys like she's like I mean if her dad's not around or like I don't know
But if you because it doesn't say you passed away
But something's like you got like her family her brothers and shit like there's something that happened when they were younger when they were younger
That's what it is
That's what it is. Listen, I don't want to get too in-depth with this.
I'm just reading the cards. Does that make sense? I don't want to fucking make, you know, because here's the thing.
What did, what did her dad do to her?
And it's not cool when she was young.
Yeah, like she is like still
Do something happen dude if I'm wrong let me know but I'm pretty sure
He's like still feeling it from when she was like a little kid something. Yeah, I don't know dude. I
Don't do I don't do three card bullshit, bro. I only read cards one way. I have seven out
Seven cards, and I'm stop getting through them right now. There's fucking I went I've gone through four
I'm working my way to the end
So just fucking bear with me here and but yeah
Just let me know if I'm wrong or right
That's crazy
Okay, so then okay. Well, that's stepdad then if she remarried that's a stepdad so that person whoever whoever her father figure was
When she was younger is fuck the fuck the shit up, dude
So
I got his next one here
No, this is a
Is going from
Either this is like
Those ones were for the past because I mean that it's not me. It's fucking I'm trying to go off this to Kate Kate's vibes
It's her fucking shit and but she's like wanting to like get out of it
She's like falling she's wanting to like be like done with some situation like she wants to be outside like open
About it open about it
and talk about it. She wants to talk about it. Whatever is going on, dude.
So...
And, uh,
in a way,
I don't know what, like, seriously.
In a way, she, like, she, like, uh...
knows she's like he knows like a
This is gonna happen
Meaning
Like she wants to talk about something
But she's like, I don't know if it's embarrassed. I mean am I being is this accurate or not because I'm fucking if I'm not dude
He's like and almost if she embarrassed something with her with one of her father, dude
She's embarrassed to talk about it with somebody
Because it's gonna change and it's gonna cause a lot of a lot of shit
It's gonna like it's gonna fucking it's gonna be like something's gonna happen and she's like
It's good. Like, you know, I don't she's like afraid
but
Yeah, did that make is that am I accurate here or not cuz I'm done if not I'm done
She's like she's like got something something in her past that she's like fucking not talking about
No, well
Not crash out, but does she have something that you know, well obviously if she does she's not gonna fucking say it
She has something in her past that she's like she doesn't she doesn't want to talk about it, but she does at the same time
That's a problem that's a problem, bro
You're asking if she's gonna do anything or whatever. Well, she's got this fucking she's got this mental fucking from her when she was young
Dude, I don't know what I'd like. I don't know what it is
She's got some fucking thing when she was younger and it's showing like a father figure. I
Mean, it's like maybe that's why I thought about it like her, you know, I
Mean multiple ones multiple ones with and then she's got a she's got siblings. I don't know how many but like
She's got brothers and sisters and like they
Like they they know about it
because this guy was a this whoever this would be her father dude or whoever this person that I'm talking about the father figure
Like fucking was like me like a mean like I don't know. Was it something like did he like uh, I don't why I want to say like
Did he fucking like smoke cigarettes?
That's what it looks like. He looks like a like a smoker like smoke cigarettes and like fucking like a fucking like mean person, dude
That's okay. So let me go from there
And she's like, she's just like holding it.
She's like, yeah, she was holding this in
because she's like, she's biting her tongue
because she doesn't want to talk about it.
Multiple, multiple fucking like multiple tongues.
Like, I don't know what that means.
Like, so somebody else knows about it.
Like probably her fucking siblings know about it.
So there's multiple people that are like also
not talking about it.
Yeah, I don't know she's a
Like it's a rebellious person like rebellious person. She's rebellious
She's got a
I mean, she's like I don't know if she's got religion, but she's like she's like got like the I mean, I don't know if this is Kate
She's got this you got it like she's like she's got the devil with her dude
She's like a devil on her shoulders, dude right now
And she's like there's two people like I don't know who they are, but there's two people that she
wants to like to play
To like play that play the devil. She's like wants to be like the evil one and like I don't know if it's revenge
But she like doesn't like these two people
And wants to like fucking like
like go ha ha ha ha
I mean, that's that's that's what I'm getting
She's like the arcade is a I don't know she's like is he like I don't she's like in the goth
Or she's into like something she's into like does she
I think she might have a mental
she like got like a mental like maybe like a disability and
I almost know what it is hold on. It's like this. She is she I want to die
Like an epileptic is she up a kid epileptic or something to do with like a having
With their arms is that a way arms
or something
Where she's like something said she's got pain
that
She's like, uh, I don't she doesn't want revenge, but she's uh, she's had a flopped up past
But yeah, she's got a
Just down
Weird I can like almost feel I gotta get it. Let me man, dude
She's got yeah, she's got
I don't know what to say, dude. Well, what I'm reading Charlie's
friends, Kate's cards, dude, and he says that I'm uh, I
Know I suck dude like a CS. I'll leave dude. I'm just I wanted to read Charlie's cards or Carly Charlie's friends
is a
You know why not and but yeah, she uh
Yeah, she needs uh, I don't know what she needs bro. She's she's
There's somebody there's two people in her and Kate's like Kate's life
That she's just like wants to like hang
Like or something
Like not only she wants to like that some some somebody somebody fucking did her did her wrong and she wants to like fucking get
Rebate like I'm not gonna say revenge because she doesn't want revenge. I don't know what she wants, but yeah, that's it
Yeah, well Tommy like
Psyche fell asleep and like if people try to join they're just gonna be go backstage because I
Can't let them come on to the streamer unless Psyche wakes up and fucking does it himself. You know what I mean?
No, I don't I don't I don't know what the fuck it ain't I'm not up. I don't know what to tell Charlie I
Don't know what you need. I'm just reading the cards. That's all I did
Don't ask me for fucking any advice on anything
I don't know
I don't know what but yeah, I'm just reading the card that's but she's got a
Yeah, she's got something that she's like always like always and she's always like has a pain somewhere dude
She always has a pain like I know it's like in her arms
You got a pain it is like she's like that's why she's like she's like something's wrong
Like she has to deal with this shit like every day
Like that what's her name Kate is like it's like it's not her fault dude. It's not her fault. You tell her it's not her fault, dude
You know it's just it's fucking uh, you know and she knows she knows it's not her fault
So that's it
Fucked up some people are fucked up, dude
Now you're talking
Yeah, it's not her fault dude. She's like she's sitting. She's sitting on something
That she's like from when she was younger dude from like, you know, I don't know. I know I don't want it is
And she's like fucking she thinks like you people have told her that she's like
You know, well if you this and that like, you know, if it wasn't for this and that you're you know
And she like fucking it. She's like been fucked like yell that
By the whoever that was whoever it is
You know almost brainwashed to where she you know, she she thinks that she's she's like
The one in fault and she's not she thinks I understand like these motherfuckers are whoever did that dude
Yeah
Yeah, I
Don't even I don't know who this I don't who this the card read I just did on the person but uh
Charlie's a friend Kate which he wanted me to read you know the card read and I just did it and then that's what I got out of it
So there you go if it's wrong, then I'm sorry if not then
It is what it is dude
And just the way that the with the vibes I get off it is just like fucking it's like damn, bro, but that sucks dude
Um
Panda brand a panda, bro
Where is there Vegas?
Is that
What's up fuzzy
Hey, I might I might start my stream to dude my I'm trying to get my computer fixed, dude
It's still fucked. So I might have to stream on my phone on the buster fucking rumble shit
because, yeah, she stays in an abusive relationship
because she's like, I don't want to say used to it,
but that's like, that's the way that she knows how,
that's the way that she knows how, she thinks it's normal.
She thinks that's how like, you know,
that's how she, somebody did the same thing in her past to her.
So she's like, oh, this is how like all guys are.
And she's like, yeah, yep.
Yeah, I mean there's multiple apps you can get depending on what platform you want to stream on, you know
Oh, it's fucking the hard drives going out like when I,
I'm surprised it even booted up right now to desktop.
When you, like right now it's like sitting to desktop.
If I go to move my mouse, the whole computer will freeze
for like 15 seconds.
And then if I, you know, and then it'll unfreeze,
I'll be able to click something or whatever.
And then it'll like start loading to like, you know,
opening it up a window and then also, oh, froze.
You know and then like and then it's and then sometimes it'll recover and be fine
For like a day and then like, you know another time I'll turn it back on and then it'll fucking start doing the same shit
So it's like yeah, it's obviously the hard drive
Going out or like some overheating hard drive, which is not overheating
It's like I like I said, it's a mechanical hard drive and it's all this shit
So it's about time for it to pop. So like I want to get an SSD
I just haven't got one yet, but I mean if I can somehow get it might shit to work like right now because it's on desktop
If I can get it to like run I'll I'll stream with it freezing like this because I'm gonna get a new hard drive and put
That new operating system like I want to get a terabyte SSD and put a new one on there anyway
Like I don't there's nothing I have on this hard drive that I you know
Need to save like if I have to wipe it fuck it
Yeah, I mean I could try let me try that, you know Brian, let me try that and
I
Feel like when I try to go get into that get into that it's gonna freeze as I'm doing that
But hey Charlie, I mean that's I mean is that pretty accurate or is it the fucking you know
That's what I got off it. Let me go over here
Yeah, something something I hit something hard because I got I got some super vibes
Yes
Yeah, I wish you guys could come up or whatever.
Let me see here.
Because I do have system restores that I've saved manually
on here, dude, but let's try to get to them.
See, I just hit the Search button by Start button,
and I went to type in system restore, and it froze.
Like the buttons the letters system didn't even type out on the thing
Oh there went now finally recovered now frozen in
Yeah, there it goes
I don't want to create a restore point, but yeah.
Yeah, I know, right?
Let me try to set some restorers,
see if I can even get to it.
Yeah.
Right?
I know I've made system restore points
on this fucking hard drive,
and when I go to it, it says the restore,
system restore, no restore points
have been made on your computer system.
Which is bullshit.
Wait, wait, wait, let me click click. What's one is it?
And it throws again give it a second
Well, yeah, I have a another hard drive it's a size is 256
Solid state which I could put windows on but I'm just gonna wait to get the terabyte
Yes, you haven't I've been working dude. I haven't had time to like fuck with this
Because I you know, I didn't think it was even gonna boot to Windows
Because it fucking hasn't
And I use nothing backup dude
There's nothing on really on this hard drive except for settings that I have an OBS for streaming
That I'm gonna have to redo and then I have a couple of
Private world of Warcraft servers that I'm gonna have to like
redo that and
Everything else
Where's my
There's really nothing I want to say
This ain't the first time this shit's happened to me either dude. I've lost
Multiple hard drives lost hella fucking pitchers in the past. So it's like nothing new
Nothing
You want me to go to safe mode and then try to get into the system
Restore
Yeah, you know it's crazy bro bright Maya the date and time
Not the date, but the date says January 15th, 2085.
And I know that's probably like a, what's it called?
The battery on your motherboard, which I put a new one in.
I have other batteries I can put in there.
That couldn't be the reason.
I mean
What's that battery called on your motherboard?
Because why wouldn't my date change is it is my hard drive that fucked up where it's corrupt
Why would my date change
Yeah, that's it.
We'll see you later.
great
Well, yeah, by the way this I don't have this connected to the internet this computer this desktop
and there's no wireless on the desktop on the motherboard,
there's no wireless like act like there's no way you can connect.
Well, that'd be cool if that's the case because I could just like,
okay, so is it, it's not,
it's F10, F8 to get into the safe mode.
I can start, try to start a safe mode.
Then go to sister store and maybe see if
The restore points that I've made because I know I've made them are there is that which suggesting because I'll try it
Let's do it
It's an aces aces fucking motherboard, so what is the fucking because I don't want to do it twice
Oh, it's not escape it's F8
F8, start in safe mode.
Let's see if we can get that far.
If we get that far.
Then,
I'll try to go to the same thing.
For the try.
I'm restarting right now and it's like taking forever.
I'm going to try to use F8 and start it in safe mode.
It just went in and capping. Come on, baby.
Okay, I just got into the boot the boot the boot sequence
So I'm able to okay guys got I think I would have hit f8 f8 brought up the guy didn't boot sequence
and if I want to install Windows again, I mean, listen, dude, hey, Brian, you got a Discord, bro, I'm going to get off, uh, uh, what's his names?
I'm going to get off his, uh, his stream, dude.
Psychstream, I'm going to get off, dude. Nobody gives a fuck about this, you know what I mean?
So, I'm on somebody else's channel, like, fucking, I'll talk, you got to, if you got a Discord, let me get on, I'll get on Discord and we'll talk, talk to you.
Cause I mean, fuck it, I have nothing else going on.
Today, today, today, today, today, Junior.
You gotta look at me now, well, shit, dude.
You gotta Instagram or like somehow we can like,
I'm not gonna give you my phone number.
So like, how can we talk on the internet besides that?
Well, I know, I mean, I haven't,
here's the thing, dude, I haven't,
this is the first day that I've tried to like fix this problem
with my desktop because I've been busy, dude.
My homie Wappy, bro.
Wappy will help me fix this, dude.
I was actually trying to think about
maybe going to his house.
because
Yeah, psych not it off and like I'm still here on a stream. That's why I'm saying I'm gonna leave you
But yeah, another thing another thing Brian did like
Only have emails or fuck then
But I don't I don't have this desktop connected to the internet. So
Yeah, and like the internet my internet that I have I can't connect it right now
So that's what I was talking about this will my buddy WAP I
Was actually thinking about like taking this whole tower to his house
That way I because we can we can fucking reinstall it and all that shit and like get all the windows updates
Get everything I get need to get done with the internet because like right now my internet is down
That's why I'm on my phone. I'm using fucking mobile data, dude. I'm on my phone
Taco hey get some fucking carne asada tacos with the pico de gallo some tapatio
Yeah, no
I love Mexican food, man. It's my favorite shit, though.
Yeah, we'll see let me try to get in the I'm at my bios right now
This isn't this isn't getting wolf. I'm in my bios. I mean, how do I get into safe mode?
Dude I can just like restart it and then click like when it goes to the where you put your fucking password in just start in safe mode
I don't need to get my BIOS.
I didn't change anything.
My shit is DELETE or F2.
to get into the BIOS.
Yeah, too late to see if it had already restarted
and it's trying to go to Windows.
There it is, a Rizer.
That's it. That's my uh, that's I kind of use
Preparing automatic repair when I when I boot up the windows when it when it goes to windows
It tries to go to the repair which I don't want to do and I'm fucked
It's not that big of a deal dude like I don't care
I got my phone with like why like data
What I was thinking to do though
Because I already have a USB drive with Windows 10
Boot up fucking shit that the files
So I need to like go back into like restart the computer again
Change the boot menu from my my C drive to fucking
the USB
And it'll go to the USB first and then it'll fucking ask me if I want to reinstall and I'll be able to choose what drive
And I can reinstall it on my other my SSD instead
I get let me just do that because it's like fucking it's like furlough right now. I've already been through this shit
Let it try to that's gonna take fucking help I mean I could let it it's gonna take like forever probably
it literally froze right now I haven't touched it I restarted it I went into the BIOS and did nothing
and then I tried to boot the windows again and it like now it's like at a black screen
and I'm looking at my uh what's it called the uh hard drive like the light that flashes when it
like when it the hard drive is working it's like not even on but then it just comes on so let me see
Now it's loading.
See what it gives us?
Diagnosing your PC.
This is going to take hours only.
I want it to be quicker just to reinstall.
I guess I could let it go. I mean, today, what's today, what time is it, but I was just like,
I was like hyped up because I was able to get to desktop, normally haven't gotten this far.
Repairing disk errors, this might take over an hour to complete.
So I could let that go, I guess.
I don't know, I get almost a guarantee that it's just...
I feel like I'm gonna let this go for like 10 hours,
and then it's gonna like, it'll freeze at the screen.
Like, it won't even like get through it.
That's what I think.
What if it does?
Oh, well, you fucking need this.
Yeah, in a way Brian, you're right all of my other hard drives that went out like they just went out and
Like you can't even like get into windows
Yeah
Or actually know what no they the way that I noticed that they were going out
Is that what try to access because I had them had them partitioned?
And I had some shit like videos and shit saved on like the other partition
And I would try to like go into those folders and it would just like it would like double click and it would just like load
super slow loading
And then it would finally like load in there and then I would like it would take forever to like load thumbnails
and shit like that
That's how that's how I noticed that they were going out. Yeah
But then after that that should just fucking didn't even boot up
Yeah, or fucking a bro go to you know if I don't have a rumble account just go to my rumble dude and
What if I when I stream just talk to me in chat?
Chris K Buster on rumble no spaces
Right, I'm going to bro live stream advertisement reddit
That's what I'm gonna do man. I just I got to get the I
Had a bunch of bills that I had to pay and
I'm broke right now
But yeah, I want to get a hard drive like on Amazon or like even go to Best Buy. It's like 60 bucks for a one terabyte
Western digital solid state
And I want to throw that in there, which I have a solid state 256.
Uh, was it Samsung?
Yeah, Samsung. No, whatever it is.
In there now, because I installed like certain games like Grand Theft Auto and Rust.
On the solid state, because I wanted to like get into the games faster.
So, and it's only 256, which I can like fucking reinstall Windows 10 on that 256 solid state right now, if I wanted.
I have the USB ready to go with the Windows files,
just boot to the fucking USB stick,
and then fucking install Windows on the 256 SSD.
But I know I'm going to get a terabyte SSD,
and I want to just wait until I get that terabyte,
and then fucking put it on that one instead.
Over the fucking,
because I want to have a terabyte of fucking,
Over the fucking 256. I mean because it's I mean, yeah
Yeah, what brand what brand did you get Brian what brand SSD do you suggest? I mean, I know Samsung dude Samsung
Western digital those are the top those are the top two in my opinion
Yeah
Yeah, Western digital
All the mechanical hard drives I've had in the past were Western digital. I mean most of them
They all they all went out
But I mean I still
Yeah, I wouldn't buy like, you know, you can buy some buster one bro
Some fucking off-brand Chinese brand, you know or whatever. I mean, they're all you know
She's probably all made in China anyway, but you know, I mean like
Pay you know pay for what you get you pay you know pay you know a couple 20 bucks more
and you'll get yourself a hard drive that's not going to fail, type shit, over a fucking, you know what I mean?
Me too, pretty much.
Me too, Brian. Western Digital, I've been using those like my whole life.
I mean, that's the hard drive that I'm, that I think's going out, is a Western Digital.
Yeah.
It's not
Yeah, that's good. It ain't a heat problem dude
Because I was like thinking to myself I was like either hard drives either over heating or failing and I know it's not a heat problem all the fans
all the fans that have been working for like five years plus are
Still working and moving the same speed that they used to spend five years ago
So yeah
It's it's just you know, I think it's going out
What's it happens
Nice
Yeah, I've always used Intel
Processors
But I used to like use radion fucking
Radion fucking video cards, dude, I used to be like a fucking I used to like a
Like now, you know g-force Nvidia or fucking radion. I would always like get the radion over the fucking
Over the Nvidia dude, but now I like switched like I'm in video all day because the video is like fucking
It is the better now it right now like fucking they're they're fucking doing work in video is like the number one
GPU
Out there dude
Like I want me is radion is ati radion still fucking in business like they're done
Nvidia just cornered the market
But yeah, that's what I have right now
Yeah, I have an i7 by the way the CPU in this is an i7 it's an I don't forget what generation but it's an i7
the
this computer, bro, this computer has
7000 whatever dude RPM. It's a 7000 RPM like one terabyte Western digital mechanical hard drive is where is what the hard drives?
I don't I'm talking about
So it's a mechanical hard drive. It's old. Yeah, it's like fucking. I don't even know how old you maybe
10 plus
Yeah
so it's it's bound to happen bro
It's like you know imagine like imagine still using a fucking mechanical hard drive dude and yeah, I that's what I that's why I got
That's why I got a little buster
256 gig solid state just to install a couple games on that. I want to fucking like play faster
And like load in too faster. So yeah
Anyways, I need to get I need to get off fucking what's his name?
Thanks fucking shit, bro. I
Do I have I have actually I haven't have an external
Western Digital 4 terabyte
External Drive, it's USB
And it's fine. It's like, you know plugs in with USB
But I don't have my OS on that I just have a bunch of bullshit that's I'm saying I have a bunch of bullshit on that hard drive
And I'll just, you know, by reinstalling the operating system, I'm not going to even fuck with that external fucking shit, I'll just unplug it, bam, it's gone.
Yeah, I don't even fucking remember what I what are they?
Am I that external Western digital I have it has just a bunch of bullshit like old cell phone pictures like that
It's fine though. Yeah hard drive still fine
Nothing
All right, listen, I'm gonna I'm gonna leave dude chat. I'm out bro. Sorry to fucking a
Fucking be boring or whatever dude, I'm out but a good time you guys good time you Brian and a live stream advertisement guy
And Charles who I was talking to earlier bro and psych if you're fucking if you're white rewatch this bro, I
Talk to you later, dude. I might be up. I'm gonna try to fuck around my computer right now, and I might be up later on
But yeah, I'm out guys
Thanks for the help Ryan
Yeah, like if you want, you know, yeah, if you want to talk to me, dude, just go to my fucking rumble, dude
Go to rumble.com and fucking if you have an account follow me
Chris K Buster I
Might stream like literally in like an hour